[
  {"question":"What Letter Comes Next In The Following Sequence \"B, C, C, D, D, D, P, R\" 'Blitzen, Comet, Cupid, Dancer, Dasher, Donner, Prancer, Rudolph, Vixen'' \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["V= Santa's Reindeers in Alphabetical Order"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of the following was not one of the Three Kings? \"Balthazar\" - \"Melchior\" - \"Soloman\" - \"Caspar\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Soloman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From the Christmas Carol \"Good King Wenceslas\", where was Good King Wenceslas the King of?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bogemia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Hot cockles\" was popular at Christmas in medieval times What was it? \"A Drinking Song\" \"A Medievil Game\" \"A Dish Of Seafood\" \"A Hot Spice Drink\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Tudor Game"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many gifts Would you receive if you received all the gifts in the song \"The 12 Days Of Christmas\") Is It 196, 296, 364, 398 \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["364"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Charles Dickens' \"A Christmas Carol\", how many different ghosts visited Scrooge?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song 'Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas' what \"will be out of sight\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Troubles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song 'Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer' how is his nose described? \"You would even say it ___\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Glows"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the movie \"It's A Wonderful Life\" how do you know that a new angel has received his wings? (\"a cock crows, there is a lightening flash, a bell rings, a trumpet sounds\") \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Bell Rings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Movie \"Miracle On 34 th Street\" Kris Kringle Is Hired To Play Santa Claus In Which Department Store Is It FAO Swartz, Marshall Field's, Macy's Or Gimble's?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Macy's"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the song \"The Twelve Days Of Christmas\", what did my true love give to me on the 12th day?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["12 Drummers Drumming"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who or what is Santa's Little Helper?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Their Pet Dog"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which famous Christmas Song is a snowman pretended to be \"Parsons Brown\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winter Wonderland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which year Was The Band Aid Single \"Feed The World Released for The 2nd Time\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["1989"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Macaulay Caulkin's folks left him \"Home Alone\" in the original 1990 movie Where did they go? \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On the Single \" Do They Know It's Christmas \" Only One Person Performed On Both The Original And The 20 Year Remake Band Aid 20, Who Was It?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bono / U2"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The carol 'Silent Night' was first played on what instrument? \"Harpsichord,Guitar,Pipe Organ, Piano\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Guitar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The words \"Myrrh is mine, its bitter perfume breathes of life, of gathering gloom___\" come from which Christmas carol?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["We Three Kings of Orient Are"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'NN' Is \"ABCDEFGHIJKMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ & ABCDEFGHIJKMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Noel Noel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What brought Frosty the Snowman to life? (\"Pixie Dust, A Kiss,Magic Snow,An Old Silk Hat\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Old Silk Hat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Eighth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["8 Maids A Milking"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Eleventh\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["11 Pipers Piping"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Fifth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Gold Rings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"First\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Partirdge In A Pear Tree"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Fourth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["4 Calling Birds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Nineth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["9 Ladies Dancing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Second\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["2 Turtle Doves"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did my true love give to me on the \"Seventh\" day of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["7 Swans A Swimming"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Sixth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["6 Geese A Laying"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Tenth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["10 Lords A Leaping"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Third\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["3 French Hens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Twelth\" Day Of Christmas\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["12 Drummers Drumming"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What drink was adapted to become the American Christmas drink 'Egg Nog'? Scandanavian Drink Glogg , Austrian Drink Gluwein, French Drink \"Lait De Poule\" The German Drink \"Biersuppe\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["The French Drink Lait De Poule"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the connection between \"Comet\", \"Cupid\" and \"Vixen\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["All Names Of Santa's Reindeers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Toy That Arnold Schwarzenegger Desperately Tries To Get For His Son For Christmas In the Film \"Jingle All The Way\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turbo Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the origin of The X In \"Xmas\"? \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["X is the first letter of the word christ in latin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Native Language Would Jesus Christ Have Spoken ? (\"Hebrew, Sanskrit, Arabic, Aramaic\" ) \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aramaic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What town is the setting for the perennial Christmas classic 'It's a Wonderful Life'? (\"Bailey Park, Beford Falls, Sleepy Hollow, Pottersville\") \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bedford Falls"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The Character That Henry Travers Plays In The Movie \"It's A Wonderful Life\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Clarence Oddbody"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When are the '12 Days of Christmas'? \"Dec 14th - Dec 25th) - (Dec 21-Jan 1) - (Dec 26 - Jan 6) - (Christmas Eve-Jan 4th) \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["(Dec 26 - Jan 6)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When visiting Finland, Santa leaves his sleigh behind and rides on a: \"BroomStick, Rudolph, A Goat Named Ukko, A White Goose\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Goat Named Ukko"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas poem does this line belong to? \"With peace on earth, good-will to men!\" (\"Christmas Bells\", \"The 3 Kings\", \"A Christmas Carol\", \"Nativity\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Bells"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which diarist noted on 25th December 1662, \"(Christmas Day). Had a pleasant walk to White Hall, where I intended to have received the communion with the family, but I have come too late___\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Samuel Pepys (pronounced 'peeps')"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which former star of 'Crossroads'' Played \"Meg Richardson\" And was born on 25th December,1923\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Noel Gordon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Is The Only Football Team In The 2006/2007 Premiership Which Doesn't Contain Any Of The Letters Of \"Santa\" In It's Name?\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liverpool"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of the following places is NOT a real U.S. city or town? \"Noel,Missouri\" - \"Santa Claus,Georgia\", \"St Nicholas Florida\", \"Snowflake,Texas\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Snowflake, Texas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of these was not one of the twelve apostles ? \"Jason,Bartholomew, Phillip, Thaddaeus\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jason"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Oscar Winning Actor Played Scrooge In \"The Muppet Christmas Carol\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Caine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which popular Christmas song was actually written for Thanksgiving? (White Christmas, Jingle Bells, Silent Night, Away In A Manger\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jingle Bells"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who banned Christmas Carol's in England between the years of 1649 and 1660? \"Oliver Cromwell\", \"King Charles II\", \"Queen Victoria\", \"Queen Elizabeth I\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Cromwell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the Christmas Cracker? (\"George Cracker\", \"Tom Smith\", \"Thomas Edison\", \"John Bell\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Smith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Is The First Ghost To Appear To Scrooge In \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marley's Ghost"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the elf called Patch in the film 'Santa Claus: The Movie'? \"Danny De Vito\" - \"Michael J Fox\" - \"Bob Hoskins\" - \"Dudley Moore\" \"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dudley Moore"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the author of \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Dickens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote The Christmas Story \"The Snowman\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raymond Briggs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote the Christmas story, \"The Snowman\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raymond Briggs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"'Afternoon Delight'' was the only major hit for which one-hit-wonder group?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Starland Vocal Band"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Arnold Schwarzenegger made his film debut in 1974 In What Movie *", "answer":0, "answers":["*Pumping Iron.*"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many people resided in the Brady house on The Brady Bunch?*", "answer":0, "answers":["9"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The war in Vietnam ended with the fall of Saigon in what year?*", "answer":0, "answers":["1975"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 70s blockbuster included the music, 'Cantina Band' by Mecco?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Star Wars"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 70s television show launched the career of David Cassidy?*", "answer":0, "answers":["The Partridge Family"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What arcade game became a hit in 1973*", "answer":0, "answers":["Pong"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What creature attacked President Jimmy Carter in a boat in 1979?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Duck"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What movie earned Steven Spielberg his first hit in 1975?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Close Encounters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the computer in TV's Wonder Woman?*", "answer":0, "answers":["IRAC"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the scandal that forced President Nixon to resign?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Watergate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What were the 'character' names of the 3 lead women of Charlie's Angels? (PFE)*", "answer":0, "answers":["Sabrina, Kelly, Jill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who loves ya, baby?'' was the catchphrase of which `70s TV sleuth?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Kojak"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Expletive Deleted' came into fashion as a result of the publication of the transcript of what?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Watergate Tapes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Is this the real life, is this just fantasy', is the opening line of which hit song?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemian Rhapsody"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Witchy Woman' was a hit for which American group in the 1970s", "answer":0, "answers":["Eagles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"13th July 1955 saw the last execution of woman in Britain - who was she", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruth Ellis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"1954 again - in which English city did Roger Bannister become the first man to run a mile in under 4 minutes", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxford (Iffley Rd)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"1955 saw the first ever Disneyland open in which U.S. state", "answer":0, "answers":["California (Annaheim)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"1955 saw the worst ever disaster in motor racing history when a Mercedes Benz hurtled into the crowd at which French race track, killing 86 people in total", "answer":0, "answers":["Le Mans"], "source":""},
  {"question":"1957 and the first artificial satellite to be launched into space (by the Soviet Union) had what name", "answer":0, "answers":["Sputnik 1"], "source":""},
  {"question":"1970 Saw Which Treaty Between USSR & Germany", "answer":0, "answers":["The Moscow Treaty"], "source":""},
  {"question":"21 October 1805 Is The Anniversary Of Which Famous Battle", "answer":0, "answers":["Trafalgar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"3 Singers Have Sung The Opening Line The Christmas Favourite Do They Know Its Christmas (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Young, Kylie Minogue, Chris Martin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"A German tradition is to hide a certain food in a Christmas tree, and the first one to find it gets a special gift. What is the certain food they hide?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Pickle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"A lot of men end up in the hospital casualty department at Christmas time because they've decorated their nether regions with what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sprigs Of Holly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"A mysterious cloud of pesticide and radiation causes a disturbing reversal for Scott Carey in which classic 50s film ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Incredible Shrinking Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to 'A Christmas Song'', what would you find roasting over an open fire", "answer":0, "answers":["Chestnuts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to some legends, what holiday decorating practice is attributed to spiders?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tinsel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the Bible who is Jesus's father", "answer":0, "answers":["God"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the bible, who are Gaspar, Balthazar and Melchior", "answer":0, "answers":["Three Wise Men"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the bible, who were the baby Jesus's first visitors", "answer":0, "answers":["The Shepherds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the Christmas song what was the only present asked for? 2 Front Teeth, 5 Bath Cubes, 4 Bars Of Soap, 3 Pairs Of socks", "answer":0, "answers":["2 Front Teeth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to The Everly Bros What Time Did Suzie Finally Wake Up", "answer":0, "answers":["4 O Clock"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the lyrics of the famous Christmas song, what was Frosty The Snowman's nose made from?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Button"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the lyrics of the song Mr Who? Was asked to turn on his magic beam", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr Sandman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the nursery rhyme, who, 'sat in the corner eating a Christmas Pie''", "answer":0, "answers":["Little Jack Horner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According To The Song How Many Drummers Drumming Were There", "answer":0, "answers":["12"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["Five Gold Rings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"According to the UK National Meteorological Office what year (prior to 2007) was the last White Christmas in Britain?", "answer":0, "answers":["2004"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After Henry VIII, Who Was The Next Member Of British Royalty To Get Divorced?", "answer":0, "answers":["Princess Margaret"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After Much Legal Wrangling Who Became The Controller Of 'The News Of The World'' In 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Rupert Murdoch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After the fall of the iron curtain, Russian leader Mikhail Gorbachev introduced a period of restructuring known as ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Perestroika"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After the fall of the manchu dynasty, there existed three political parties in china: The KMT, Nationalists and The ______ ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Communists"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After The Fire made 'Der Kommissar' popular, but which eighties musician performed it originally?", "answer":0, "answers":["Falco"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After which famous person in history was the teddy bear named?", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After who was America named?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amerigo Vespucci"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After who was Mickey Mouse named?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mickey Rooney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"After years of flirtation, the U.S. began direct military involvement in Vietnam in what year?", "answer":0, "answers":["1964"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Alanis Morrisette appeared on what 80's cable children's show?", "answer":0, "answers":["You Can't Do that On Television"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Alexander the Great was king of which country ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Macedonia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Alphabetically Which Is The Last Of Santa's Reindeers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vixen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Alphabetically, Which Is The Last Of Santa's Reindeers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vixen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Also In 1968 Which British Coin Was Introduced To Replace The Ten Shilling Note", "answer":0, "answers":["50 Pence Piece"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Also known as the 'Isle of Apples', Christ and Joseph of Aramathea travelled here in ancient times.", "answer":0, "answers":["Avalon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Amityville House On The Hill' was sung by who in 1986", "answer":0, "answers":["Lovebug Starski"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Another plane crash, on February 3rd 1959, resulted in the deaths of which three rock stars of the day", "answer":0, "answers":["Buddy Holly, Big Bopper, Richie Valens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Apart From Anthony Perkins Which Other Performer From Psycho Also Appeared In Psycho 2 (23 Years Later)", "answer":0, "answers":["Vera Miles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", "answer":0, "answers":["160"], "source":""},
  {"question":"April 1889 Saw The Birth Of Which Future Dictator?", "answer":0, "answers":["Adolf Hitler"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Arnold Schwarzenegger is a father trying to get the must have toy, Turbo Man, in which 1996 film", "answer":0, "answers":["Jingle All The Way"], "source":""},
  {"question":"As at November 2005, who is the only British Prime Minister to have been appointed and dismissed four times, serving four separate terms in office?", "answer":0, "answers":["William Gladstone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"As what was Istanbul previously known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Constantinople"], "source":""},
  {"question":"As what was Taiwan formerly known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Formosa"], "source":""},
  {"question":"As what was winchester known by the Romans?", "answer":0, "answers":["Venta Bulgarum"], "source":""},
  {"question":"At Christmas, it is customary to exchange kisses beneath a sprig of which plant?", "answer":0, "answers":["Missletoe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"At the time of Julius Caesar, who was the ruler of Egypt ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cleopatra"], "source":""},
  {"question":"At which battle did Nelson famously (turn a blind eye) to orders to disengage?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Battle of Copenhagen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"At which battle was the Charge Of The Light Brigade?", "answer":0, "answers":["Balaclava"], "source":""},
  {"question":"At which hospital was the first British Heart Transplant operation performed in 1979?", "answer":0, "answers":["Papworth, Cambridge"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Axl Rose was an anagram for what phrase?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oral Sex"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Bashful, Doc, Dopey, Grumpy Are 4 Of The Seven Dwarfs Name The Other 3 (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Happy, Sleepy, Sneezy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Before she was a pop star, why was Samantha Fox in the British tabloids?", "answer":0, "answers":["She was a page three girl"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Beginning in the 1820s, who from the southeastern united states were relocated to indian territory over numerous routes", "answer":0, "answers":["The five civilized tribes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Between which countries was the shortest war in history?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zanzibar and England"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Biko was involved in what protest movement?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apartheid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Bing Crosby famously sang 'I'm dreaming of a white Christmas'', what is the next line.", "answer":0, "answers":["Just like the ones I used to know"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Born Florian Armstrong, on Christmas Day 1971, which female singer dueted with Eminem on the 2000 hit 'Stan''", "answer":0, "answers":["Dido"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Born on Christmas Day 1887, this American tycoon, created one of the largest hotel chains in the world (Surname)", "answer":0, "answers":["Conrad Hilton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Born on Christmas Day 1899, which actor starred in 'Casablanca'' and 'The Big Sleep''", "answer":0, "answers":["Humphrey Bogart"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Born on Christmas Day 1954, who was the female half of the 80's band 'The Eurhythmics''", "answer":0, "answers":["Annie Lennox"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Britain and Argentina fought over these islands in 1982.", "answer":0, "answers":["Falklands Islands"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Britain's first stretch of motorway was opened in 1958 to bypass which northern town (now a city)", "answer":0, "answers":["Preston"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"By what name was Baron Manfred von Richthofen better known?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Red Baron"], "source":""},
  {"question":"By who was Gerald Ford almost assassinated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Squeaky Fromme"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Calpurnia Was The 3rd Wife Of Which Roman Emperor", "answer":0, "answers":["Julias Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Canadian Prime Minister: Pierre Elliott __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Trudeau"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Charlie Chaplin Died On Christmas Day In 1977, How Old Was He When He Died", "answer":0, "answers":["88"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Child star Jimmy Boyd sang which hugely popular 1950's Christmas song, which was initially banned by the Catholic Church in Boston because it supposedly mixed sex and Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["I saw Mommy kissing Santa Claus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Chrissie Hynde was in which early eighties group?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pretenders"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Christmas Crackers is cockney rhyming slang for which part of the male anatomy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Testicles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Christmas Island Is A Territory Belonging To Which Country", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Churchill, F.D. Roosvelt and Stalin met here in 1945.", "answer":0, "answers":["Yalta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Clement C. Moore wrote a very famous Christmas poem What was it called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twas The Night Before Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Cleopatra's slaves often died because she tested this on them", "answer":0, "answers":["Poison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Complete the verse - 'Twas the night before christmas, when all through the house. Not a creature was stirring not even a", "answer":0, "answers":["Mouse"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Complete this quote: 'I feel the need___ the need for___'", "answer":0, "answers":["Speed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Composer George Gershwin died in1937 at the age of 38. How did he die?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brain Tumour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Considered to be the last full blooded Tasmanian aborigine, (died 1876 - aged 73), her name is_____?", "answer":0, "answers":["Truganini"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Currently the world's longest serving leader, he ousted General Batista in January 1959 - who is he", "answer":0, "answers":["Fidel Castro"], "source":""},
  {"question":"David Hasselhof spent most of his time driving a car on which eighties tv show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Knight Rider"], "source":""},
  {"question":"December 26th is known as Boxing Day but it is also which Saints Holy Day", "answer":0, "answers":["St. Stephen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"December 26th is traditionally known as Boxing Day but it is also which Saints Holy Day", "answer":0, "answers":["Saint Stephen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Deriving its name from the Latin word meaning knowledge and a Greek word meaning branch of learning which church was founded in 1954 in California, moving it's headquarters to Sussex in 1959?", "answer":0, "answers":["Church of Scientology"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Designed By Robert Fulton, Which Weapon Was Tested In The Seine In 1801?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Submarine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Dia de los Muertos (The Day of the Dead) is celebrated in which Latin American country", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Don Mintoff became which countries first Prime Minister after it became a republic in 1974?", "answer":0, "answers":["Malta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Double, double toil and trouble, Fire burn, and cauldron bubble. Comes from which of Shakespeare's plays\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Macbeth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Dr. Christian Barnard performed the world's first ever what in South Africa in 1967.", "answer":0, "answers":["Heart Transplant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"During which conflict is The Caine Mutiny' set?", "answer":0, "answers":["World War 2"], "source":""},
  {"question":"During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles II"], "source":""},
  {"question":"During Which Monarch's Reigns Did Shakespeare Live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth I & James I"], "source":""},
  {"question":"During Which War Did The Charge Of The Light Brigade Occur?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"East Berlin was the capital of ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["East Germany"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Electric Christmas tree lights were first used in what year? 1878,1895, 1903, 1907", "answer":0, "answers":["1895"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Elizabeth I was the daughter of which king?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry VIII"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Elvis Presley Died On August 16th 1977 But Where EXACTLY Was He When He Died", "answer":0, "answers":["On The Toilet"], "source":""},
  {"question":"England Opened Its First Nudist Beach In 1979 At Which Seaside Resort", "answer":0, "answers":["Brighton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Eras are divided into units called ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Periods"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Ex tv detective, turned crooner. Who sang Silver Lady?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Soul"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Famed as a member of the Rat Pack, who died on Christmas day 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Dean Martin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"February 6th 1958 saw a plane carrying Manchester United home from a match in Belgrade crash during take-off at which city's airport", "answer":0, "answers":["Munich"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For how many years did the 30 Years War last? 27, 30 or 36?", "answer":0, "answers":["30 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For what country did Columbus make his historic voyage", "answer":0, "answers":["Spain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For what country did Columbus make his historic voyage?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For what is the eighteenth and nineteenth century sailor Sir Francis Beaufort best remembered?", "answer":0, "answers":["His System Of Wind Force Indicators"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For Which Allegedly Obscene Publication Were 'Calder & Boyars'' Prosecuted In 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Last Exit To Brooklyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For Which Crime Was 'Thomas McMahon'' Jailed For Life In October 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["Mountbatten's Murder"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For which European country did Mozambique declare independence in 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["Portugal"], "source":""},
  {"question":"For which label did Elvis first record?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sun Records"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Formed in 1955, with which island was the organisation known by the acronym EOKA associated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cyprus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Four Japanese carriers were destroyed in this battle.", "answer":0, "answers":["Midway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Frankish ruler Charles the Great is better known as _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlemagne"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands", "answer":0, "answers":["Denmark"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands?", "answer":0, "answers":["Denmark"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From what did Alexander the Great suffer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Epilepsy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From what were Jack-o-Lanterns first made in U.K.", "answer":0, "answers":["Turnips"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From Which Country Did Saint Nicholas Originate", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From Which Country Does The Poinsettia Plant Originate", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From which country does the poinsettia plant originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From which era does the custom of carol singing originate? (Edwardian, Victorian, Middle Ages)", "answer":0, "answers":["The Middle Ages"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From which film do we get the song 'White Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["Holiday Inn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"From which phrase is the word Halloween Derived", "answer":0, "answers":["All Hallows Eve"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Gangster Al Capone, boss of the Chicago underworld, was finally gaoled for 11 years for what crime?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tax evasion"], "source":""},
  {"question":"General Sherman burned this city in 1864.", "answer":0, "answers":["Atlanta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"George Washington Carver advocated planting peanuts and sweet potatoes to replace what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cotton and tobacco"], "source":""},
  {"question":"George Washington Carver advocated planting what to replace cotton and tobacco?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peanuts and sweet potatoes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Germany was split into two zones by which agreement?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yalta agreement"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Romania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Germany's WW I allies were Austria_Hungary, Bulgaria, and ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Germany's WW I allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Ghost Town' was the only number single released by which British band", "answer":0, "answers":["Specials"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Godzilla first made his mark so to say in 1954. What do the Japanese call Godzilla ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gojira"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Good King Wenceslas was a 12th Century king of which country", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Good King Wenceslas was king of which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Good King Wenceslas Was The Duke & Later King Of Where?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Grease The Musical Opened On Broadway In 1973 How Many Performances Were There", "answer":0, "answers":["3,388"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Greased Lightnin was taken from the film Grease, but who had chart success with it?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Travolta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Great Britain Was The First Country To Issue Postage Stamps But In What Year", "answer":0, "answers":["1840"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Halloween is celebrated on the eve of what Christian holiday is it A All Saints Day B St Swithins Day or C Feast of the Tabernacle", "answer":0, "answers":["A = All Saints Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Halloween originated from a festival celebrated by what ancient European tribe is it A Druids B Huns or is it C Celts", "answer":0, "answers":["C = Celts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Halloween originated from which Pagan festival", "answer":0, "answers":["Samhain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He advocated the planting peanuts and sweet potatoes to replace cotton and tobacco.", "answer":0, "answers":["Carver"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He allowed the bugging of the Democratic Committee headquarters.", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Nixon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He discovered the Grand Canyon.", "answer":0, "answers":["Francisco Coronado"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He is a pumpkin whose top and stem have been cut out and interior removed, leaving a hollow shell that is then decoratively carved. Twelve Letters", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack O' Lantern"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He is identified with the expression, \"Eureka\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Archimedes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He is said to have fiddled while Rome burned.", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He killed Jesse James.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ford"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Jones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He ordered the persecution of Christians in which Peter and Paul died.", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1964 for his civil rights leadership.", "answer":0, "answers":["Martin luther king jr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He ruled Rome when Christ was born.", "answer":0, "answers":["Caesar augustus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He said, \"I have nothing to offer but blood, tears, toil and sweat.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir winston churchill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He shot Lee Harvey Oswald.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Ruby"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He shot Lee Harvy Oswald.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruby"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He taught Alexander the Great.", "answer":0, "answers":["Aristotle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City.", "answer":0, "answers":["John lennon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963.", "answer":0, "answers":["John fitzgerald kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn.", "answer":0, "answers":["General custer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was stabbed by Cassius.", "answer":0, "answers":["Julius caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was stabbed by Gaius Cassius Longinus.", "answer":0, "answers":["Julius Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was the American inventor of the Cotton Gin.", "answer":0, "answers":["Whitney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was the captain of the \"Mayflower\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Standish"], "source":""},
  {"question":"He was the U.S. president during the Civil War.", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham Lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Henry The 8 th Had A Bit Of Bad Rep When It Comes To His Wives But He Only Executed 2 (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn, Katheryn Howard"], "source":""},
  {"question":"His ship was the H.M.S. Beagle.", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Darwin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"His wife was Roxana, his horse was Bacephalus, he was?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alexander the Great"], "source":""},
  {"question":"His wife was Roxana. His horse was Bacephalus. He was ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Alexander the great"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Holy Roman Emperor Charles VI created which principality in 1719?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lichtenstein"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How are Caspar, Balthazar and Melchior better known", "answer":0, "answers":["The Three Wise Men"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Did Darth Vader Know What Luke Skywalker Got For Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["He Felt His Presents"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How did John Belushi die?", "answer":0, "answers":["Drug and Alcohol overdose"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How did the bum convince the family dog to start eating again in Down and Out in Beverly Hills?", "answer":0, "answers":["He ate the dog's food"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How did the tradition of serving turkey at Christmas originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Medievil Europe serving Large Fouls Was A sign Of Wealth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Did UN Secretary General Dag Hammarskjoeld Die In September 1961", "answer":0, "answers":["In An Air Crash"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How do you write 69 in Roman numerals?", "answer":0, "answers":["LXIX"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Does Good King Wencelesas Like To Eat His Pizza", "answer":0, "answers":["Deep Pan Crisp And Even"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How in the world of music is Richard Starkey more commonly known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Is St Sylvester's Day Otherwise Known?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Years Eve"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How is the stockmarket collapse of the 24th October 1929 better known ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black Thursday"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Long Did The 100 Years War Last", "answer":0, "answers":["116 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How long does it take a Christmas tree to grow before it's harvested?", "answer":0, "answers":["6-8 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Long Was The American Civil War", "answer":0, "answers":["Four Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Long Was The Hundred Years War?", "answer":0, "answers":["116 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many astronauts manned each Apollo flight", "answer":0, "answers":["3"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many astronauts manned each Apollo flight?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many astronauts manned each project mercury flight", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many British officers were forced by Indian troops into the Black Hole of Calcutta?", "answer":0, "answers":["146"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Children Did Queen Victoria Have", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Colonies Signed The American Declaration Of Independence?", "answer":0, "answers":["13 Colonies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many countries joined the United Nations at it's start ?", "answer":0, "answers":["51"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Crusades Were There?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Days After Hiroshima Did Nagasaki Receive The Second Atom Bomb", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many days after john f. kennedy's assassination was lee harvey oswald shot", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Films Were Made In The Jaws Series", "answer":0, "answers":["4 (Jaws 1,2,3 & Jaws The Revenge)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many ghosts appeared to Scrooge in Dicken's 'A Christmas Carol''", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many gifts are given in total in the song The Twelve Days of Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["364"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many gloves did Michael Jackson wear?", "answer":0, "answers":["One"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Gold Rings In Total Did My True Love Give To Me (Think About It)", "answer":0, "answers":["40 (5x8=40)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Men Were There In A Roman Legion?", "answer":0, "answers":["6000"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many oklahoma land runs were there", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many people were killed in the battle of Lexington?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Pilgrims Were Aboard The Mayflower", "answer":0, "answers":["120"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Points Does A Snowflake Have", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many points does a snowflake have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many presidents of the United States fought in the Civil War?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many reindeer does Santa Have?", "answer":0, "answers":["8 / (9 With Rudolph)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Ships Came Sailing In On Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many sides does a snowflake have? 6,8,10,12", "answer":0, "answers":["6"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many spirits appeared to Ebenezer Scrooge in Charles Dickens' A Christmas Carol?", "answer":0, "answers":["4, Jacob MarleyPast Present Future"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many stab wounds did Julius Caesar have when he died ?", "answer":0, "answers":["23"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many states did richard nixon carry in 1972", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty nine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many times was franklin roosevelt elected president", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Many Times Was Queen Elizabeth I Married", "answer":0, "answers":["None"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many wise men where there?", "answer":0, "answers":["3"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many witches in a coven", "answer":0, "answers":["13"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many witches were burned at the state in salem, massachusetts", "answer":0, "answers":["None"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many years was Nelson Mandela in prison?", "answer":0, "answers":["27"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How many years were between the creation of the Magna Carta and the American Declaration of Independence ?", "answer":0, "answers":["561"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How old was Alexander the Great when he died ?", "answer":0, "answers":["32"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was Edward VI When He Became King?", "answer":0, "answers":["9 Years Old"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was Elvis Presley When He Achieved His First UK No.1 With 'All Shook Up''", "answer":0, "answers":["22"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was James Dean When He Died", "answer":0, "answers":["24"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was John F Kennedy When He Was Assassinated", "answer":0, "answers":["46"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How old was John F. Kennedy when he became president", "answer":0, "answers":["43"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How old was John F. Kennedy when he became president?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty three"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was Margaret Thatcher When She Took Up The Role Of British Prime Minister In 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["53"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Old Was Playboy Founder Hugh Hefner When He Launched The First Edition Of 'Playboy''", "answer":0, "answers":["27"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How old was Stanley Matthews when he retired in 1965?", "answer":0, "answers":["50"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How old would Elvis have been on his birthday January 8, 2000? A=55, B=60, C=65", "answer":0, "answers":["C=65"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How Was Mistletoe Known By The Vikings Who Discovered It, Was It Snow Berries, Love Berries, White Tear Drops Or Dung on A Stick?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dung On A Stick"], "source":""},
  {"question":"How was the 1839-42 Anglo-Chinese war better known ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Opium War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Humphrey Bogart, who was born on Christmas Day 1899, said the line 'Here's looking at you kid.'' In which film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Casablanca"], "source":""},
  {"question":"I Am A Suburb Of California, I Have The Nickname (Surf City) and part of my name sounds the same as the surname as 2 Famous Hollywood Celebrities, Where Am I", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Cruz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"I Love The Dead', 'Call It Evil' and 'Prince Of Darkness' are all singles released by whom", "answer":0, "answers":["Alice Cooper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If a girl puts the letters of the alphabet face down in water, how will she know who she will marry", "answer":0, "answers":["His initials will be face up next day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If a turkey evades the oven, what is its normal lifespan", "answer":0, "answers":["12 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If an Italian gave you Smeg for a present, what would it be?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Kitchen Appliance"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If one takes inflation into account, which 1960's film was the most expensive film ever made ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cleopatra 'On your knees!!!'"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If someone gave you a frumenty at Christmas would you eat it, drink it or wear it", "answer":0, "answers":["Eat It (A spiced porridge)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you attended a Swedish Christmas Party and were given 'Glogg'' what would you do with it, eat it, drink it or put it on your head", "answer":0, "answers":["Drink it, it's a hot spiced drink made from wine or spirit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you found a button in your Christmas pudding what would it symbolize Good luck, Poverty, Bachelor, Famous", "answer":0, "answers":["A Bachelor"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you kiss someone under the mistletoe, what should you then remove", "answer":0, "answers":["One of the berries (for good luck)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you licked Mr T's booty, it would taste like___", "answer":0, "answers":["Sexual Chocolate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If You Were Born On Christmas Day What Star Sign Would You Be?", "answer":0, "answers":["Capricorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you were born on Christmas Day, what would your star sign be?", "answer":0, "answers":["Capricorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you were born on Halloween, what star sign would you be", "answer":0, "answers":["Scorpio"], "source":""},
  {"question":"If you were offered a 'spotted dick' after Christmas dinner, what could you expect?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Steamed Pudding"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In _Rocky,_ what does Apollo Creed's trainer warn him about Rocky Balboa?", "answer":0, "answers":["He's Left Handed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 'A Christmas Carol'', what is Tiny Tim's surname", "answer":0, "answers":["Cratchett"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 'Bridget Jones Diary'', Bridget Jones makes a New Years Resolution, to sort out her life, meet a man and keep a diary, but who played Bridget Jones", "answer":0, "answers":["Renée Zellweger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 'Home Alone 2'' which city was Kevin lost at Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["New York"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 'Sixteen Candles', what did the geek need to get to prove he had sex (which he got from Molly Ringwald)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Underpants"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1453 it is alleged that a witch flew on a broomstick for the first time but was it a male or female witch", "answer":0, "answers":["Male"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1613 Who Did Pocahontas Marry", "answer":0, "answers":["John Rolfe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1647, the English parliament passed a law that: Let Prisoners spend Christmas At Home, Gave Santa Immunity To Burglary, Made Christmas An Official Holday, Made Christmas Illegal", "answer":0, "answers":["Made Christmas Illegal"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1692 The Witchcraft Trials took place in America. Where", "answer":0, "answers":["Salem, Massachusetts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1715 Louis XIV Of France Was Succeeded By Louuis XV What Relation Was He", "answer":0, "answers":["Great Grandson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1785, Blanchard and Jeffries became the first to cross the English channel using which method of transport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Balloon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1816 which US state was admitted to the Union as the 20th state?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mississippi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1840 London Sweet Maker Tom Smith Came Up An Invention Still Hugely Popular Today What Was It?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Christmas Cracker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1893, this country was the first to give women the vote.?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1902 this volcano erupted, killing 30,000", "answer":0, "answers":["Pelee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1902 this volcano erupted, killing 30,000.", "answer":0, "answers":["Pelee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1911 Roald Amundsen became the first person to reach where ?", "answer":0, "answers":["South Pole"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1921 Who Founded The First Birth Control Clinic In London", "answer":0, "answers":["Marie Stoppes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1939 which pub game was banned in Glasgow for being too dangerous?", "answer":0, "answers":["Darts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1950 which French designer created the so-called New Look", "answer":0, "answers":["Chriatian Dior"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1951 Howard Hawks Produced The Thing. Who Directed The 1982 remake, Starring Kurt Russell", "answer":0, "answers":["John Carpenter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1951 Howard Hawks produced The Thing. Who directed the 1982 remake, which starred Kurt Russell", "answer":0, "answers":["John Carpenter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1952. 'Elizabeth Becomes Queen'. Who was her late father?", "answer":0, "answers":["George VI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1953 'Stalin Died'. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", "answer":0, "answers":["Khrushchev."], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1953 Queen Elizabeth II was crowned following the death of her father George VI but what was his 'proper'' first name David - Albert - Louis - Edward - George\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Albert"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1953 Science fiction author L.Ron Hubbard founded which cult religion, one of who's prominent modern day followers is John Travolta", "answer":0, "answers":["Scientology"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1954 Roger Bannister achieved the worlds 1st Sub 4 min mile in what English County did this take place", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxforshire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1954 the Salk vaccine was introduced - a vaccine which effectively wiped out which devastating disease", "answer":0, "answers":["Polio"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1956, Tunisia gained independence from which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["France"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1957, who left the music business to become a preacher.", "answer":0, "answers":["Little Richard"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1959 Who Established A Communist Government In Cuba", "answer":0, "answers":["Fidel Castro"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1959, Berry Gordy Jr. started a small record company called", "answer":0, "answers":["Motown"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1959, Tibet was invaded by which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["China"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1960 Penguin Books Announced That They Would Be Publishing Which Controversial Novel", "answer":0, "answers":["Lady Chatterlys Lover"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1960 who did Bobby Darin marry.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sandra Dee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", "answer":0, "answers":["Concorde"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1968 Which Country Did The USSR Invade To Stamp Out Liberal Reform", "answer":0, "answers":["Czechoslovakia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1969 Richard Cawston Made A Documentary For The BBC About Which Famous Family", "answer":0, "answers":["The Royal Family"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1972 which flash new motor was advertised with the slogan, ` The car you always promised yourself'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ford Capri"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1972 which flash new motor was advertised with the slogan, `The car you always promised yourself'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ford Capri"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1974 who was sacked from his position of England football manager?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alf Ramsey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1975, what re-opened after an 8 year closure?", "answer":0, "answers":["Suez Canal"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1976 which computer company was set up by Steven Jobs and Stephen Wozniak, marketing the first open system machine in 1977?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apple"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1978 which famous comedy returned for a second series, four years after the first had been shown", "answer":0, "answers":["Fawlty Towers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1978 which famous comedy returned for a second series, four years after the first had been shown?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fawlty Towers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1979 which English art historian was exposed as a one-time Soviet spy and stripped of his knighthood?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anthony Blunt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1979 who was revealed to be the fourth Russian spy in the Burgess, MacLean and Philby affair?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anthony Blunt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1979, Jeremy Thorpe was found not guilty of plotting to murder whom?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norman Scott"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 1986 the prime minister of which European country was assassinated on his way home from the cinema with his wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sweden (Olof Palme)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In 70's CB Radio Slang What Is A 'Smokie''", "answer":0, "answers":["A Policeman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In a 60s film, who was the bravest of them all ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance (Gene Pitney)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alaska"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Charles Dickens' novel A Christmas Carol, who was Scrooge's dead business partner?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In cockney rhyming slang what are 'Mince Pies''", "answer":0, "answers":["Your Eyes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In December 1967 53 Year Old Louis Washkansky Became The First Person To Undergo What", "answer":0, "answers":["A Heart Transplant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In England Children Traditionally Put Out A Christmas Stocking For Santa, But In Holland What Do Dutch Children Traditionally Put Out For Santa To Fill", "answer":0, "answers":["A Clogs Or Sabots"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In film, the very secretative Alex Leamas came from where?", "answer":0, "answers":["In from the cold. The Spy Who Came In From The Cold ."], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Finland Santa traditionally doesn't use his sleigh what does he ride instead, is it, Rudolph, Santa's servant Black Peter, A goat named Ukko or Thirteen Elves", "answer":0, "answers":["A goat named Ukko"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Halloween, Michael Meyers wore a Halloween mask of what famous character", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Kirk mask"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Halloween, what is the middle name of Michael Myers", "answer":0, "answers":["Audrey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Harry Potter And The Goblet of Fire, What ingredient was needed to resurrect the dark lord", "answer":0, "answers":["Blood of an enemy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Holland, Santa traditionally doesn't actually deliver the presents who does, is it, Rudolph, Santa's servant Black Peter, A goat named Ukko or Thirteen Elves", "answer":0, "answers":["His servant Black Peter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In March 1979, where did a major nuclear accident occur ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three Mile Island"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Medievil England What Name Was Given To The Area Presided Over By A Lord", "answer":0, "answers":["Manor"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In pantomime what is Alladin's surname", "answer":0, "answers":["Twankey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Sabrina The Teenage Witch What Is The Name Of Sabrina's Cat", "answer":0, "answers":["Salem"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Scotland, what vegetable was traditionally carved into a jack-o-lantern was it A Potato B Turnip C Pumpkin", "answer":0, "answers":["B = Turnip"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 'Twelve days of christmas', how many items in total are sent by 'my true love'?", "answer":0, "answers":["78"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 15th century, what was the war between the houses of Lancaster and York?", "answer":0, "answers":["War of the Roses"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 17th century which country started taxing beards ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Russia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 17th Century, how did Matthew Hopkins become known and feared", "answer":0, "answers":["The Witchfinder General. He hung 60 witches"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 17th century, if you were given Christmas Clap off someone, what have they given you?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Kiss Under The Misletoe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 1855 Russian War, what were used to transport Torpedos ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kites"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 1946 film, It's a Wonderful Life, what's the name of George Bailey's guardian angel?", "answer":0, "answers":["Clarence (Oddbody)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 1970s films directed by Robert Fuest (Pronounced Feast) how did Dr. Anton Phibes become disfigured", "answer":0, "answers":["Car Crash"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the 9th century which city had several thousand bookstores ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baghdad"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Bible who sent out a dove to find land", "answer":0, "answers":["Noah"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Charles Dickens Novel 'A Chrismas Carol' Who Was Scrooges Dead Business Partner", "answer":0, "answers":["Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas carol 'Away in a Manger' where was the little Lord Jesus asleep on", "answer":0, "answers":["The Hay"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas carol when did 'Good King Wenceslas' look out?", "answer":0, "answers":["Feast Of Stephen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song 'Let It Snow' what was the weather described as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frightful"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song 'White Christmas' what did children listen for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sleigh Bells"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song what was 'Roasting on an Open Fire'", "answer":0, "answers":["Chestnuts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the Christmas song who 'are getting fat'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Geese/Goose"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the fairy tale 'Cinderella'', which slipper did she lose, the left or the right", "answer":0, "answers":["Left"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Film 'Halloween' For How Many Years Was The Killer Locked Up In An Asylum Before He Escaped", "answer":0, "answers":["15 Years"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the film 'The Santa Clause' who plays Santa?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tim Allen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the harbour of which city was the Greenpeace flagship Rainbow Warrior sunk in 1985?", "answer":0, "answers":["Auckland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Inspirational 1946 Film 'Its A Wonderful Life' What Is The Name Of George Baileys Guardian Angel", "answer":0, "answers":["Clarence Oddbody"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the movie 'Home Alone', Macaulay Culkin plays a boy who is accidentally left alone at Christmas. What is the name of this character?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kevin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Movie 'Interview With The Vampire' Who Played The Vampire Being Interviewed", "answer":0, "answers":["Brad Pitt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the movie 'Miracle on 34th Street', Kris Kringle is hired to play Santa Claus in what large department store?", "answer":0, "answers":["Macys"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Original 1984 Band Aid Song, 'Do they Know It's Christmas'', Who Sang The First Line", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Young"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the period 978-1016 England was ruled by which \"Unready\" king ?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Ethelred"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Song 'The Twelve Days Of Christmas' My True Love Brought Me Nine What", "answer":0, "answers":["Ladies Dancing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the song 'We wish you a Merry Christmas' what pudding was asked for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Figgy Pudding"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the song the 12 days Of Christmas what did my true love give on the 5th day", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Gold Rings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the song The Twelve Days of Christmas, '___my true love brought to me nine___' what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ladies dancing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Tradition of the song the 12 days of Christmas if you add up all the legs and take away all the beaks what number are we left with", "answer":0, "answers":["155 Confirmed by Lindsey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Tv Show Til Death Us Do Part First Aired In 1965 What Football Team Did Alf Support", "answer":0, "answers":["West Ham"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In The Ukraine what does it mean if find a spiders web In your house Christmas morning is it, good luck , bad luck, winter will be unusually cold", "answer":0, "answers":["Good Luck"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the US what was known as Armistice Day until 1954?", "answer":0, "answers":["Veterans Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the world of music how is 'Jiles P Richardson'' more commonly known?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Big Bopper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In the year 2000 which companies CEO was the worlds second richest man ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oracle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Us Dollars How Much Did America Pay Russia For The State Now Known As Alaska", "answer":0, "answers":["7.2 Million"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Victorian England what people were popularly called robins because of their red uniforms?", "answer":0, "answers":["Postmen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Century was St Nicholas first Mentioned", "answer":0, "answers":["4th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Century Were The War Of The Roses Fought", "answer":0, "answers":["15th Century"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["India"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur\"", "answer":0, "answers":["India"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what country did John Lennon and Yoko Ono start their honeymoon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Holland/Amsterdam"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what language was the (Communist Manifesto) by Karl Marx written?", "answer":0, "answers":["German"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what type of building did Plato and Aristotle teach ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gymnasium"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Us City Was President John F Kennedy Assasinated In 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas / Texas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what war did the jet fighters first battle each other?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Korean War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year did England's lease on Hong Kong expire", "answer":0, "answers":["1997"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did Great Britain Gain Control Of Hong Hong", "answer":0, "answers":["1842"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did India Gain Independence From British Colonial Rule", "answer":0, "answers":["1947"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did India Gain Independence Marking The Start Of Decolonisation", "answer":0, "answers":["1947"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year did Lord Lucan leap into obscurity", "answer":0, "answers":["1974"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year did man first set foot on the moon", "answer":0, "answers":["1969"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did Mikhail Gorbachev Become Leader Of The Soviet Union", "answer":0, "answers":["1985"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did Neil Armstrong First Step Foot On The Moon", "answer":0, "answers":["1969"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did The American Civil War End", "answer":0, "answers":["1865"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did The French Revolution Begin", "answer":0, "answers":["1789"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did The Great Fire Of London Occur", "answer":0, "answers":["1666"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did The Spanish Civil War Begin", "answer":0, "answers":["1936"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did The Vietnam War Begin", "answer":0, "answers":["1954"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did World War I Begin", "answer":0, "answers":["1914"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Did World War I End", "answer":0, "answers":["1918"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year of WW II did Russia declare war on Japan", "answer":0, "answers":["1945"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year was 'Dirty Dancing' released?", "answer":0, "answers":["1987"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was Abraham Lincoln Assasinated", "answer":0, "answers":["1865"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was Band Aids 'Do They Know Its Christmas' The UK Christmas No.1 Single", "answer":0, "answers":["1984"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year was Band-Aid's Do They Know It's Christmas the UK Christmas chart-topping record?", "answer":0, "answers":["1984"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was Queen Elizabeth The I Born", "answer":0, "answers":["1533"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was Robert Kennedy Assassinated? (2 Points Spot On, 1 Point Year Either Way)", "answer":0, "answers":["1968"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected", "answer":0, "answers":["1916"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The Chinese Republic Established", "answer":0, "answers":["1911"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year was the first Christmas card produced?", "answer":0, "answers":["1846"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In what year was the first English translation of the Bible completed?", "answer":0, "answers":["1388"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The French Declaration Of The Rights Of Man (Liberty, Equality, Fraternity)", "answer":0, "answers":["1789"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The General Strike", "answer":0, "answers":["1926"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The Old Age Pension Introduced In The UK", "answer":0, "answers":["1908"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The Tomb Of Tutankhamen Discovered", "answer":0, "answers":["1922"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In What Year Was The United Nations Organisation Formed", "answer":0, "answers":["1945"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1944 film were Trick and Treat children to be seen", "answer":0, "answers":["Meet me in St. Louis."], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1947 Christmas film do a lovestruck couple pretend that the snowman is Parson Brow", "answer":0, "answers":["Winter Wonderland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character ' Babe Levy' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marathon Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character ' Lenny Bruce' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lenny"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character 'David Sumner' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Straw Dogs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character 'Louis Dega' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Papillon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the following characters ' Carl Bernstein '?", "answer":0, "answers":["All the Presidents Men"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1971 Oscar winning film is the main character a tough, no nonsense, pork pie hat wearing New York City detective ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The French Connection"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which 1982 Film Did The Freeling Family Move To A Haunted House", "answer":0, "answers":["Poltergeist"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1984 film does the character of Billy Peltzer bring Christmas chaos to the town of Kingston Falls, when he inadvertently feeds someone he shouldn't after midnight", "answer":0, "answers":["Gremlins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which 1984 Film, Did A Young Man Called Zach, Receive A Mogwai For Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["Gremlins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1988 film remake of 'A Christmas Carol'' does Bill Murray play a cynically selfish TV executive", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrooged"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which 1998 remake did Matthew Broderick play Dr.Niko Tatopoulos (Pronounced Tat-Oh-Pool-Loss)", "answer":0, "answers":["`Godzilla'"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which American state is George A. Romero's 1968 film 'Night Of The Living Dead' set", "answer":0, "answers":["Pennsylvania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which battle was George A. Custer defeated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Battle of Little Bighorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which body of water is Christmas Island?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indian Ocean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Century Did Lady Godiva Live?", "answer":0, "answers":["11th Century"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which century was (The Black Death)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fourteenth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which century was the first pantomime in Britain", "answer":0, "answers":["18th (1717)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which Christmas song would you find the lines, 'He's making a list and he's checking it twice. He's going to know who's naughty and nice''", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Claus Is Coming To Town''"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which City Did Chamberlain Make His(Wind Of Change) Speech In 1960?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cape Town"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which city did the Duke of Windsor die in 1972?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which City Did The Indian Mutiny Start?", "answer":0, "answers":["Meerut"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which City Was John F Kennedy Assassinated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which city was President Kennedy killed", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which city was President Kennedy killed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dallas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which city were the Hanging Gardens", "answer":0, "answers":["Babylon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which city were the Hanging Gardens?", "answer":0, "answers":["Babylon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place", "answer":0, "answers":["China"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["China"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Country Did The Tradition Of Trick Or Treating Actually Originate", "answer":0, "answers":["England"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country did this practice of 'Trick Or Treating' originate", "answer":0, "answers":["The United Kingdom, surprisingly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do families dress a stuffed male doll with old clothes from each member of the family and then burn it, symbolizing forgetting all the bad things of the old year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colombia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do people eat noodles while listening to a bell start ringing and strike 108 times?", "answer":0, "answers":["Japan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do people go to the beach to jump seven waves and throw flowers in the sea while making a wish?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do people wear masks to burn on December 31 to drive away bad luck?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ecuador"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do people wear white clothes in order to have good luck during the new year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do people who want to travel take a suitcase and carry it around the house on New Year's Eve?", "answer":0, "answers":["Venezuela"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do some people eat long noodles to to wish for a long life?", "answer":0, "answers":["Japan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do they eat 12 grapes as the clock strikes midnight (one each time the clock chimes) on New Year's Eve?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country do they pound rice into a glutinous form using a huge hammer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Japan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country is a bell struck 33 times?", "answer":0, "answers":["Korea"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Country Is The Auschwitz Concentration Camp Located", "answer":0, "answers":["Poland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was Adolf Hitler born", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was Adolf Hitler born?", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was Greenpeace founded in 1971?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was paper money first used?", "answer":0, "answers":["China"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was the Rosetta Stone found", "answer":0, "answers":["Egypt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which country was the Rosetta Stone found?", "answer":0, "answers":["Egypt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Country Will You Find Lapland?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which English town was the Co-Operative Society formed in 1844?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rochdale"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which English town was William Shakespeare born?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stratford-Upon-Avon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which European city did composer Richard Wagner die in 1883?", "answer":0, "answers":["Venice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which European country did the use of Christmas trees originate", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany (5th Century)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which film does a Moloko Plus loving Ludwig van fan live with his 'M' and 'P' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Clockwork Orange"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which film is the bad guy a one handed criminal named Han who deals in drugs and white slavery ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Enter the Dragon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which Fox TV show did Johnny Dep play an undercover cop in high school?", "answer":0, "answers":["21 Jump Street"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which Hitchcock classic does James Stewart play a man hired to follow Kim Novak?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vertigo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which hospital would you find Sir Lancelot Spratt?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Swithens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which Massachusetts town were 20 people executed for witchcraft in 1692", "answer":0, "answers":["Salem"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Modern Day Country Would You Find The Region Known As Transylvania", "answer":0, "answers":["Romania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Month Of Which Year Was The Six Day War Between The Arabs & The Israelis", "answer":0, "answers":["Jun-67"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Movie Did Jim Carey Play Lloyd Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["Dumb & Dumber"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which popular 1950s film is a character played by Audrey Hepburn given 24 hours to do as she pleases in the eternal city ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roman Holiday"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Scary Movie Will You Find The Character 'Dr Egon Spengler'", "answer":0, "answers":["Ghostbusters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Scary Movie Will You Find The Character Martin Brody", "answer":0, "answers":["Jaws"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Series Of Films From 1984 Onwards Did Robert Englund Star As Freddy Krueger", "answer":0, "answers":["A Nightmare On Elm Street"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which state was `The Blair Witch Project' set", "answer":0, "answers":["Maryland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Tim Burton Film Did Johnny Depp's Character Have To Confront The Legend Of An Axe Wielding Headless Horseman", "answer":0, "answers":["Sleepy Hollow"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Tv Show Might You Encounter 'The Mystery Machine'", "answer":0, "answers":["Scooby Doo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which two continents might you find vampire bats", "answer":0, "answers":["North & South America"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which US City was Martin Luther King assassinated in 1968?", "answer":0, "answers":["Memphis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which war did Florence Nightingale earn her reputation ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which war was Bunker Hill a major battle?", "answer":0, "answers":["The American War Of Independence"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which War Was Pork Chop Hill Fought Over?", "answer":0, "answers":["Korean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Welsh Village Where 144 Adults And Children Killed By A Land Slippage?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aberton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Did A Soviet Cosmonaut Make The First Spacewalk", "answer":0, "answers":["1965"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Did Abba Win The Eurovision Song Contest", "answer":0, "answers":["1974"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Did The Battle Of Hastings Take Place?", "answer":0, "answers":["1066"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year did the demolition of the Berlin Wall begin?", "answer":0, "answers":["1989"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin", "answer":0, "answers":["1982"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Did The Oil Tanker Torrey Canyon Come Aground Near Lands End Causing A Major Environmental Disaster", "answer":0, "answers":["1967"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year did the Queen make her infamous 'Annus Horriblis'' Christmas broadcast", "answer":0, "answers":["1992"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year did the Titanic sink?", "answer":0, "answers":["1912"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year did the UK hand over Hong Kong sovereignty to China?", "answer":0, "answers":["1997 (June 30th)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Was Joan Of Arc Burned At The Stake?", "answer":0, "answers":["1431"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Was Mr Blobby A Christmas Number One In The Uk", "answer":0, "answers":["1993"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Was The Battle Of Trafalgar Fought?", "answer":0, "answers":["1805"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Was The Berlin Wall Constructed", "answer":0, "answers":["1961"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year was the Berlin Wall constructed?", "answer":0, "answers":["1961"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In Which Year Was The Law Abolished That Allowed Witches To Be Burned", "answer":0, "answers":["1736"], "source":""},
  {"question":"In which year was the Rosetta stone written ?", "answer":0, "answers":["196 BC"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Introduced in 46 BC by Julius Caesar, how many months was the Julian calendar divided into?", "answer":0, "answers":["12"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Is A Pumpkin A Vegetable Or A Fruit", "answer":0, "answers":["A Fruit It Grows On Vines"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Is an icicle a Stalagmite or a Stalagtite", "answer":0, "answers":["Stalagtite"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Is kissing under the Mistletoe, a Roman, Druid, or Celtic custom", "answer":0, "answers":["Druid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Israel occupied the Golan Heights.  Whose territory was it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Syria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Israel occupied the Golan Heights. Whose territory was it", "answer":0, "answers":["Syria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Israel occupied the West Bank.  It belonged to _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jordan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Israel occupied the West Bank. It belonged to _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jordan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown' is a critically-acclaimed and very popular animated halloween television special based on a comic strip by which American cartoonist", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles M. Schultz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Jadis the White Witch is the villain in which children's book", "answer":0, "answers":["The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"James Dean died during the filming of which film in 1955?", "answer":0, "answers":["Giant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Jesus was allegedly born on Christmas Day, what Starsign would he have been", "answer":0, "answers":["Capricorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"John Callcott Horsley designed what first commercial Christmas item in 1843?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas card"], "source":""},
  {"question":"John F. Kennedy Airport in New York used to be called __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Idlewind"], "source":""},
  {"question":"John F. Kennedy Airport used to be called __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Idlewild"], "source":""},
  {"question":"John McClane was fighting terrorists in a skyrise in which eighties movie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Die Hard"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Johnny Depp Made His Movie Debut In Which Scary Movie", "answer":0, "answers":["A Nightmare on Elm Street"], "source":""},
  {"question":"King Abdullah was assassinated in 1951. Of which country was he king?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jordan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"King Richard the ________?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lionhearted"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Legendary magician Harry Houdini died in Detroit on Halloween in 1926 but what caused his death was it A Trick went wrong B Heart Attack or was it C Ruptured Appendix", "answer":0, "answers":["C Ruptured Appendix"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Little boy & fat man were the first", "answer":0, "answers":["Atomic bombs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Live Aid was to benefit which starving country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ethopia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"London's Trafalgar Square Christmas tree is traditionally given by which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Mark David Chapman was famous for what in 1980?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shooting John Lennon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Marvin Lee Aaday Is The Real Name Of Which Rock Star Who Also Appeared As Eddie The Ex Delievery Boy In The Movie The Rocky Horror Picture Show", "answer":0, "answers":["Meatloaf"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Messala was the gad guy in which 50s blockbuster ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ben Hur"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Moondance' was a hit for which male singer", "answer":0, "answers":["Van Morrison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Muhammad Ali Took On George Foreman In The 'Rumble In The Jungle'' In what Country Did This Take Place", "answer":0, "answers":["Zaire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Mussolini invaded this country in 1935.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ethiopia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name any of James Dean's three films (Point For Each).", "answer":0, "answers":["_Rebel without a cause, East of Eden_ _and __Giant__._"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name Jacques Cousteau's research ship.", "answer":0, "answers":["Calypso"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name James Dean's three films.", "answer":0, "answers":["A Rebel without a cause, East of Eden, Giant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name Queen Elizabeth I's Mother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the 2 of the 3 flags placed by Hillary in the summit of Everest in 1953?", "answer":0, "answers":["British, Nepal and the UN"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The 8 Reindeer From 'The Night Before Christmas' Poem", "answer":0, "answers":["Blitzen, Comet, Cupid, Dancer, Dasher, Donner, Prancer, Vixen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the 80's band that named the sides of their first album Hardware and Software and also used samples from Star Trek movies in their songs.", "answer":0, "answers":["Information Society"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the author of Dracula", "answer":0, "answers":["Bram Stoker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the author of Frankenstein", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Shelley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the author of The Novel Frankenstein", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Shelly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The British Liner That Sunk On Its Maiden Voyage In 1912?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Titanic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the cartoon that featured characters who had messages on their clothes to express their feelings.", "answer":0, "answers":["Shirt Tales"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the eighties sitcom in which Bob Ueker was upstaged by an obese butler regularly.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr. Belvedere"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The Event Involving The Anarchist, Peter The Painter?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Siege Of Sydney Street"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The Fabulous Winged Horse Of Greek Mythology?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pegasus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties", "answer":0, "answers":["Tracy Ullman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the first black nation to gain freedom from European colonial rule.", "answer":0, "answers":["Haiti"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The First Steam Engine To Run Between Stockton & Darlington?", "answer":0, "answers":["Locomotion No1"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The German Battleship Sunk In A Norwegian Fjord In 1944?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tirpitz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the incident in which tea was dumped into the harbour.", "answer":0, "answers":["Boston Tea Party"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the loner rebel reindeer with the red shiny nose.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rudolph"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the original comic strip Bill The Cat appeared in.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bloom County"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the original eight reindeer from the 'Twas the night Before Christmas' poem.", "answer":0, "answers":["Comet, Cupid, Dasher, Dancer, Prancer, Vixen, Donner, Blitzen (or Dunder and Blixem)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The Queen Of England Who Ruled For Nine Days?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lady Jane Grey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the remake of a 1960's film with the aid of the following actors. The first actor was in the 60's original, the second actor played the same role in the remake David Niven and Daniel Craig", "answer":0, "answers":["Casino Royale"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the remake of a 1960's film with the aid of the following actors. The first actor was in the 60's original, the second actor played the same role in the remake James Mason and Jeremy Irons", "answer":0, "answers":["Lolita"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the remake of a 1960's film with the aid of the following actors. The first actor was in the 60's original, the second actor played the same role in the remake Robert Mitchum and Robert de Niro", "answer":0, "answers":["Cape Fear"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The Ship In Which Columbus Discovered America?", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Maria (Pinta & Nina Were Sister Ships)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the sitcom that featured Judd Hirsch, Andy Kaufman, Tony Danza and Danny Devito.", "answer":0, "answers":["Taxi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name The Slave Who Lead An Unsuccessful Revolt By The Gladiators Against Rome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spartacus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the toy that consisted of color pencils and plastic which you would put in the oven to create.", "answer":0, "answers":["Shrinky Dinks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the TV show which featured an average housewife teamed up with a secret agent.", "answer":0, "answers":["Scarecrow and Ms. King"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Name the U.S.S.R. leader with a birthmark on his forehead?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gorbachev"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Nanny, Sandra Rivett was the victim of which infamous murderer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Lucan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Near what falls did Jimmy Angel crash his plane in 1937?", "answer":0, "answers":["Angel Falls"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Near which Belarus City did the biggest ever tank battle take place during WWII?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kursk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Neil Armstrong And Buzz Aldrin Landed On The Moon But Who Stayed Behind In The Command Capsule?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Collins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Neptune Was The Roman God Of The Oceans, What Name Did The Greeks Use?", "answer":0, "answers":["Poseidon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Nicknamed the Godfather Of Soul, who died on Christmas Day 2006", "answer":0, "answers":["James Brown"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Nikolai Caucescau, was executed on Christmas Day 1989, in which former Communist country was he President", "answer":0, "answers":["Romania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Of What Tribe Was Boadicea The Head?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Iceni"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Of which Cambodian party was Pol Pot the leader?", "answer":0, "answers":["Khmer Rouge"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Of which country did Robert Menzies become Prime Minister in April 1939?", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Of which ship was Miles Standish captain?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Mayflower"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Often Played At Halloween, Which Song Was A Hit Gor Bobby Boris Picket & The Crypt Kickers", "answer":0, "answers":["Monster Mash"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Oklahoma comes from two choctaw words, okla and humma, and literally means what", "answer":0, "answers":["Red people"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Oklahoma has more man-made ___ that any other state", "answer":0, "answers":["Lakes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Oklahoma statehood in 1907 became a sure thing. in part due to the discovery of what", "answer":0, "answers":["Oil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Oklahoma's four include the ouachitas, arbuckles, wichitas, and the kiamichis.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mountain ranges"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Oklahoma's recorded History began in 1541 when what spanish explorer ventured through the area on his quest for the lost city of gold", "answer":0, "answers":["Coronado"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Old superstition Wearing socks inside out protection from what", "answer":0, "answers":["Witches"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On Dec 1st 1955 A Woman from Montgomery Alabama hit the headlines after refusing to give up her seat on a bus to make way for a white person what was her name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rosa Parks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On May 1st 1931 the world's then tallest building was opened in New York City. which building was it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Empire States Building"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On november, 16, 1907, oklahoma became the what number state", "answer":0, "answers":["46th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On the 1st of July of what year was the British colony of Hong Kong returned to China?", "answer":0, "answers":["1997"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On the 3rd January 1959 which state became America's 49th", "answer":0, "answers":["Alaska"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On the face of which mountain does the climax of North by Northwest take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mount Rushmore"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On Tv How Is Eddie Fitzgerald More Commonly Known", "answer":0, "answers":["Cracker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On Tv In The 80's What Would The Initials 'HHOH' Signify", "answer":0, "answers":["Hammer House Of Horrors"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On what date did 'The Wall' fall?", "answer":0, "answers":["1989"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On what date did America become an independant nation?", "answer":0, "answers":["July 4th, 1776"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On What Date Is Saint Stephens Day Celebrated", "answer":0, "answers":["26th Dec"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On what day of the week did Solomon Grundy die?", "answer":0, "answers":["Saturday"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On what did Marley's ghostly face first appear to Scrooge in Dickens' A Christmas Carol", "answer":0, "answers":["A door knocker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On What Japanese City Was The First Atomic Bomb Dropped", "answer":0, "answers":["Hiroshima"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On what was Pennsylvania incorrectly spelled?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liberty Bell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On which Christmas day did English and German troops play football", "answer":0, "answers":["1914"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On Which Date Does Halloween Fall", "answer":0, "answers":["October 31st"], "source":""},
  {"question":"On which date is Epiphany celebrated in the traditional Western calendar?", "answer":0, "answers":["6th January"], "source":""},
  {"question":"One who fought professionally in Roman arenas was a(n) ____________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Gladiator"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Originally native to Mexico what is traditionally known as the Christmas flower", "answer":0, "answers":["The Poinsettia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Originating from a story about an Irish blacksmith, you ran into the Devil in a pub, what name is given to a pumpkin if it has a face carved into it and is illuminated by a candle", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack O' Lantern"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Orson Wells directed Charlton Heston and Janet Leigh in which 1958 film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Touch Of Evil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Paul Anka's Puppy Love is written to what star?", "answer":0, "answers":["Annette Funicello"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Peter Jackson Is Responsible For Directing Which Famous Trilogy", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Of The Rings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Played subsequently by Sarah Michelle Geller on tv, which character was played in a movie by Kirsty Swanson", "answer":0, "answers":["Buffy theVampire Slayer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Plus or minus 100 pounds (lb), how much did the world's largest recorded pumpkin weigh", "answer":0, "answers":["1,524 lb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Pop Star Marty Wilde Had A Baby Girl In 1960 What Did He And His Wife Call Her", "answer":0, "answers":["Kim (Kim Wilde)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Presepe in Italy refers to what Christmas tradition?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nativity scene (literally meaning crib)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Queen Cleopatra proclaimed herself to be which Egyptian goddess?", "answer":0, "answers":["Isis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Released in 1978 what were the names of the two gangs which John Travolta and Olivia Newton John belonged to in the movie `Grease'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The T-Birds and The Pink Ladies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Ringing a bell on Halloween is said to do what", "answer":0, "answers":["Scare Evil spirits"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Ritchie Valens and The Big Bopper were killed in a plane crash in 1959. Which other famous singer was killed in that crash?", "answer":0, "answers":["Buddy Holly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Roman statues were made with detachable whats, so that one what could be removed and replaced by another?", "answer":0, "answers":["Heads"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Rorke's Drift was a battle in which war?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Zulu War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer was a character created in a story written in: A=1939, B=1949, C=1954,D=1959", "answer":0, "answers":["A=1939"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Samhain', literally means 'end of summer' and is a Gaelic language word. What is it's direct English equivalent", "answer":0, "answers":["November"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Santa Claus is based on St Nicholas, where was he born", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Santa Claus reportedly lives at the _____ Pole.", "answer":0, "answers":["North"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She overcame her handicaps to become a lecturer and a scholar.", "answer":0, "answers":["Helen Keller"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was called \"The Maid of Orleans\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Joan of arc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was Queen of Egypt and mistress of Julius Caesar.", "answer":0, "answers":["Cleopatra"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was the first First Lady to be received privately by the Pope.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jackie kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was the first woman premier of Israel.", "answer":0, "answers":["Golda Meir"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was the first woman to fly the Atlantic solo.", "answer":0, "answers":["Amelia Earhart"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was the first woman to swim the English channel.", "answer":0, "answers":["Gertrude Caroline Ederle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She was the greatest trick shot artist of all time.", "answer":0, "answers":["Annie Oakley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"She won the 1979 Nobel Peace Prize for her work among the poor.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mother Teresa"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Since 1923, the National Christmas Tree on the White House lawn has been lit every year _except _ one. What year was that, and why wasn't it lit?", "answer":0, "answers":["John F Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Sir Henry Morgan was a famous 17th century___?", "answer":0, "answers":["Buccaneer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Sir Stamford Raffles founded which minor Asian nation?", "answer":0, "answers":["Singapore"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Snarf' and 'Liono' are both characters from what famous 80s cartoon show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thundercats"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Soleil Moon Frye was the real name of which young eighties sitcom star, whose character name was also the title of the show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Punky Brewster"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Southern Rhodesia became what country in 1980?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zimbabwe (Independent Nation of Zimbabwe)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.", "answer":0, "answers":["Cuba"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Sputnik 2 Was Launched Into Space In 1957 What Was The Name Of The Dog That Was On Board", "answer":0, "answers":["Laika"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Strawberries are the undoing of an unhinged man in which 50s film ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Caine Mutiny"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Sugar and ground almonds are the ingredients for which part of a Christmas cake", "answer":0, "answers":["Marzipan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Talking of Holland, traditionally Santa doesn't actually deliver the presents who does, is it, Rudolph, Santa's servant Black Peter, A goat named Ukko or Thirteen Elves", "answer":0, "answers":["His servant Black Peter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Thanksgiving has traditionally been the start of the Christmas season in the U.S. Which U.S. President moved Thanksgiving up a week to extend the holiday shopping season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frankiln Delano Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The _____ universe was replaced by the Copernican universe.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ptolemic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The ______ Tea Party?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boston"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The \"Bay of Pigs\" fiasco took place in this country.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Cuba"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The 14th July 1789 marked the start of what ?", "answer":0, "answers":["French Revolution"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The 1954 movie White Christmas was the first to be made using what new Paramount film format?", "answer":0, "answers":["VistaVision"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The American comedian and actor William Claude Dukenfield, died on Christmas Day in 1946. How was he better known?", "answer":0, "answers":["WC Fields"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The American M4 tank is better known as what?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sherman tank"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Battle of Rorke's Drift in 1879 featured in which war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zulu War (or Zulu Wars)."], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Beatles Were One Of The Biggest Phenomenon's Of The 1960's But Who Was Their Manager", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Epstein"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The birthplace of Napoleon, also the capital of Corsica, is?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ajaccio"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Character 'Jack Skellington' Appears In Which 1993 Film", "answer":0, "answers":["The Night Before Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Character Jack Skellington Appears In Which 1993 Tim Burton Film?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Nightmare Before Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Character Of Mike Myers Features Heavily In Which Series Of Horror Movies", "answer":0, "answers":["Halloween"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Charge Of The Light Brigade Occured During Which War", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Christmas carol 'Away In A Manger'' … what is a manger", "answer":0, "answers":["A Feeding Trough"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Christmas period of 1813-14 saw the last what in London?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Fair on a frozen River Thames (known as a Frost Fair)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Christmas story is only told in two of the four gospels, Luke is one which is the other", "answer":0, "answers":["Matthew"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Christmas Tree Displayed In Londons Trafalgar Square Is Traditionally Donated By Which Country", "answer":0, "answers":["Norway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The collective noun for a group of witches is a ____ of witches.", "answer":0, "answers":["Covern"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Colosseum received its name not for its size, but for a colossal statue of who that stood close by?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Cranberries song 'Zombie' was released in which year", "answer":0, "answers":["1994"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The current image of Santa Claus as a plump man with white beard and red and white tunic dates from a 1931 Advertising campaign, for which product", "answer":0, "answers":["Coca-Cola"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The date of which Christian festival was fixed in 325AD by the Council of Nicaea?", "answer":0, "answers":["Easter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Deaths Of 3 Pop Icons Was Known As 'The Day The Music Died'' Name The Three (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Buddy Holly, Richie Valens, Big Bopper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Devonian Period is also known as the Age of __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Fish"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Eldest Sons Of The Kings Of Which Country Had The Title (Dauphin)?", "answer":0, "answers":["France"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The fear of halloween is known by which other name (Fourteen letters)", "answer":0, "answers":["Samhainophobia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The festival of Halloween was first celebrated by which ancient tribe", "answer":0, "answers":["The Celts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The first charity Christmas card was produced by UNICEF in 1949. The picture chosen was painted by a: A Chimp, A 7 Year Old Girl, A Pop Star, A Buddhist Monk", "answer":0, "answers":["A 7 Year Old Girl"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The first dog in space was named _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Laika"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The first ever Olympic Games to be held south of the equator opened in which city in 1956", "answer":0, "answers":["Melbourne"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The first successful organ transplant occurred in 1954. What organ was it A= Kidney, B= Liver, C= Heart?", "answer":0, "answers":["A= Kidney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'Blessed are the cheese makers' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Life of Brian"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'Is it safe' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marathon Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'It's as big as a house' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Close Encounters of the 3rd Kind"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'It's pronounced Fronkensteen' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Young Frankenstein"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'There're all gonna laugh at you' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carrie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'You Came In That Thing, You're braver than I Thought' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Star Wars"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Taxi Driver"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you're gonna need a bigger boat' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jaws"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The following is a line from which 1970's film My name is___. 'Names is for tombstones baby' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Live and Let Die"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The four Sundays before Christmas are known by what name", "answer":0, "answers":["Advent (Sundays)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The General Strike, Called In 1926, Supported Which Union?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mine Workers Union"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Gold Coast gained its independence from Great Britain in 1957 and renamed itself as what", "answer":0, "answers":["Ghana"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Greek army under Leonides was annihilated here by Persians in 480BC.", "answer":0, "answers":["Thermopylae"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Halloween Tree' is a 1972 fantasy novel by which American author", "answer":0, "answers":["Ray Bradbury"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The horse Khartoum plays a 'deciding' role in which classic 70's film ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Godfather"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Inquisition forced him to recant his belief in the Copernican Theory.", "answer":0, "answers":["Galileo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The invention of what in 1867, made Alfred Nobel famous?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dynamite"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The land that would eventually be known as oklahoma was part of the what in 1803", "answer":0, "answers":["Louisiana purchase."], "source":""},
  {"question":"The last line of this document is \"Working men of all countries, unite.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Communist Manifesto"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Mask In The Film Scream Became A Popular Costume What Famous Painting By Edward Munich Was It Based On", "answer":0, "answers":["The Scream"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The massacre at Kent State occurred as students protested the bombing of Cambodia and the _____ war.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vietnam"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Monument in the City Of London is a monument to which event?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Great Fire Of London"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The most famous indian relocation to oklahoma was by the cherokee indians, what was the route called", "answer":0, "answers":["Trail of tears"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The name of which place of biblical significance actually means 'House of Bread''", "answer":0, "answers":["Bethlehem"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Nordic countries (Denmark, Sweden, Norway notably) tend to celebrate Christmas chiefly on which date?", "answer":0, "answers":["24th December"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The official song and anthem of the state of oklahoma is ___,composed and written by richard rodgers and oscar hammerstein", "answer":0, "answers":["Oklahoma"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The original Halloween film directed by John Carpenter in 1978 cost just $320,000 to make. It ended up making how much world wide was it A 40M, B 50M or was it C 60M", "answer":0, "answers":["B (50 Million)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Romans built these to convey water.", "answer":0, "answers":["Aqueduct"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The second line of which carol is '… When they are both full grown''", "answer":0, "answers":["The Holly & The Ivy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Simpsons Halloween Episodes are an annual tradition in which there are three separate, self-contained pieces. By which title are these episodes known", "answer":0, "answers":["Treehouse of Horror"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Song 'White Christmas ' Was' Performed In Which 1942 Film", "answer":0, "answers":["Holiday In"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The song White Christmas was first performed in which 1942 film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Holiday Inn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this city.", "answer":0, "answers":["Chicago"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The state motto for oklahoma is labor omnia vincit, which means what", "answer":0, "answers":["Labor conquers all things"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The three buildings of the Acropolis are the Propylaea, the Erectheum, and the _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Parthenon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The three wise men allegedly brought gifts of Gold, Frankincense and Myrrh, spell Myrrh", "answer":0, "answers":["Myrrh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Tradition Of Dressing Up On Halloween Started Because", "answer":0, "answers":["It Was Believed If You Looked Like A Ghost Then You Would Be Tormented By A Real One"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The two crooks in the 1990 film 'Home Alone'', one was Daniel Stern, who was the other", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Pesci"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The USA's official National Christmas Tree is in which National Park?", "answer":0, "answers":["King's Canyon National Park, California"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The video for which eighties song features nothing but 5 cheerleaders?(Name the artist too)", "answer":0, "answers":["Mickey Toni Basil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Wars of the Roses (1455-85) were fought between which two houses of England?", "answer":0, "answers":["York and Lancaster"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The world was declared safe from which virus in 1979, after it had killed more than 1 billion people?", "answer":0, "answers":["Smallpox"], "source":""},
  {"question":"The Worlds First Travel Agency Was Founded In 1850 By Whom?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Cook"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Then name Santa Claus is derived from which language, is it Dutch, French or Italian", "answer":0, "answers":["Dutch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Theodor Geisel published an easy reading book for kids, featuring a cat. How is he more commonly known", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Seuss"], "source":""},
  {"question":"These fighters always began a bout by saying, \"Hail Emperor, those about to die salute you.\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gladiators"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This assassin of Julius Caesar was his friend.", "answer":0, "answers":["Brutus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ming"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This European war was named after a peninsula between the Black sea and the sea of Azov?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This F.B.I agent headed the investigation of Al Capone.", "answer":0, "answers":["Elliot ness"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This fearsome creature lived on Grympen Myre and was the principal character in which book", "answer":0, "answers":["The Hound Of The Baskervilles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This French peasant girl led the army to victories.", "answer":0, "answers":["Joan of Arc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This frontiersman and politician was killed at the Alamo.", "answer":0, "answers":["Davey crockett"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Indian group ruled in early Peru.", "answer":0, "answers":["Inca"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This is said to be history's greatest military evacuation.", "answer":0, "answers":["Dunkirk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This military attack took place on Dec. 7, 1941.", "answer":0, "answers":["Pearl harbour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Nazi leader had his six children poisoned prior to his own death.", "answer":0, "answers":["Joseph Goebbels"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This organization was founded by William Booth.", "answer":0, "answers":["Salvation army"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Queen of France was beheaded in 1793.", "answer":0, "answers":["Marie antoinette"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This racist organization was formed in Tennessee in 1865.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ku Klux Klan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Roman killed himself after his defeat at Actium.", "answer":0, "answers":["Marc Antony"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Sioux Indian toured with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sitting bull"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This Spaniard conquered Mexico.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hernando Cortez"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This U.S. President suffered from polio during WWII.", "answer":0, "answers":["Franklin D Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This U.S. president was fatally shot in 1881.", "answer":0, "answers":["James Garfield"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This U.S. Secretary of State won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973", "answer":0, "answers":["Kissinger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This U.S. Secretary of State won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973.", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry Kissinger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This war began on June 25, 1950.", "answer":0, "answers":["Korean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This was the largest real estate deal in U.S. history.", "answer":0, "answers":["Louisiana purchase"], "source":""},
  {"question":"This word describes the Nazi annihilation of Jews.", "answer":0, "answers":["Holocaust"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Those big black CD's that you see at garage sales that people call \"albums\" are made of _____.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Vinyl"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Three of Santa's reindeers have a name beginning with the letter D, Dasher, Dancer and who else", "answer":0, "answers":["Donner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Three of the names of Santa's reindeer begin with the letter 'D'', name two of them", "answer":0, "answers":["Dancer, Dasher, Donner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Through the streets of what town did Lady Godiva ride naked?", "answer":0, "answers":["Coventry"], "source":""},
  {"question":"To What Did The Chant Hell No We Won't Go Refer", "answer":0, "answers":["The Vietnam War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"To what position was John Masefield appointed in May 1930?", "answer":0, "answers":["Poet Laureate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"To What Was Byzantium Renamed In 330 AD", "answer":0, "answers":["Constantinople"], "source":""},
  {"question":"To which island was Napoleon exiled, after his loss at Waterloo ?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Helena"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Traditional in Germany at Christmas, what sort of food is stollen?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cake"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Traditionally are the 12 Days of Christmas, before or after Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["After (26 Dec - 06 Jan)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Traditionally children in Italy and Spain don't get their presents on Christmas day. On what day do they get them, is it Christmas Eve, Boxing Day, January 1st or January 5th", "answer":0, "answers":["Januray 5th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Transformers are whats in disguise?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robots"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Two 747's collided here in 1977.", "answer":0, "answers":["Canary islands"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Two groups have had three consecutive Christmas No 1's, the first was the Beatles, in 1963-64-65, name the second", "answer":0, "answers":["The Spice Girls (1996-97-98)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"U.S. President, Chester Alan ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Arthur"], "source":""},
  {"question":"U.S. President, Herbert C. _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hoover"], "source":""},
  {"question":"U.S. President, John Quincy ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Adams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"U.S. President: Calvin _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Coolidge"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'BH' Do You Get When You Cross & Sheep With A Sweet", "answer":0, "answers":["Bah Humbug"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'C' Was A 1992 Horror Movie And A 2006 Hit For Christina Aguilera", "answer":0, "answers":["Candyman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'CE' Does Adam Call His Wife On December 24th", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Eve"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'CP' Is One Of The Ghosts From A Christmas Carol", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Present / Past"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'HHH' Does Santa Do In His 3 Gardens", "answer":0, "answers":["Ho, Ho, Ho"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'IR' Does Michael Fish Say To His Wife When The Heavens Open On Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["It's Reindeer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'MBC'' Was A Christmas Number One In December 1978", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary's Boy Child"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'NP' Is An Opinion Survery Conducted In Alaska", "answer":0, "answers":["North Pole"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'SG' Do The Salt And Pepper Say To Eachother At Christmas Time", "answer":0, "answers":["Seasons Greetings"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'SK' Do You Call A Quiet Armour Wearer", "answer":0, "answers":["Silent Knight"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 'SN' Do You Call An American Holy Man Who's Strapped For Cash", "answer":0, "answers":["Saint Nickle-Less"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 19th century war between Russia and England, Turkey, Britain and France, was named after a peninsula in the Black Sea?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What 80's game show featured the 'Whammy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Press Your Luck"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What actor was killed in a car crash on the way to participate in a sports car race?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Dean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What age preceded the Iron Age", "answer":0, "answers":["The bronze age"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What age preceded the Iron Age?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Bronze Age"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What amendment to the u.s. constitution ended prohibition", "answer":0, "answers":["The twenty first"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What American city was called New Amsterdam in the early 17th century?", "answer":0, "answers":["New York"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What American feminist went bust as a silver dollar", "answer":0, "answers":["Anthony"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What American feminist went bust as a silver dollar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Susan B. Anthony"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What animal is Snowball in George Orwell's book Animal Farm?", "answer":0, "answers":["A pig"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Apollo 13 astronaut contacted Mission Control with the words, (Houston, we've had a problem)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Swigert"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What are male witches called", "answer":0, "answers":["Warlocks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Are Monsters With Only One Eye Called", "answer":0, "answers":["Cyclops"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Are The first Names Of The Everly Bros", "answer":0, "answers":["Don & Phil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Are The Names Of The 3 Wise Men Who Brought Gifts To The Baby Jesus", "answer":0, "answers":["Gaspar, Melchior, Balthasar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Are The Names Of The Ghosts In The Classic 80's Video Game Pac Man", "answer":0, "answers":["Inky Pinky Blinky & Clyde"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What are you supposed to remove after kissing someone under the mistletoe?", "answer":0, "answers":["A berry from the mistletoe, for luck"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What asian leader was known as the little brown saint", "answer":0, "answers":["Mahatma gandhi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What automotive flop was named for the only child of henry ford", "answer":0, "answers":["The edsel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What band got their name from the sixties movie Barbarella?", "answer":0, "answers":["Duran Duran"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What battle of the war of 1812 wa fought after the treaty of ghent was signed", "answer":0, "answers":["The battle of new orleans"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Became America's 50th State On August 21st 1959", "answer":0, "answers":["Hawaii"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Became The Tallest Building In England In October 1965", "answer":0, "answers":["Post Office Tower"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What black muslim leader was assassinated on feb. 21, 1965", "answer":0, "answers":["Malcolm x"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What came to an end in the United States in December 1933?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prohibition"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Canadian sketch comedy show helped launch John Candy's career?", "answer":0, "answers":["SCtv"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What caused the computer in Electric Dreams to become alive?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spilled Champagne"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What caused the gremlins in the movie Gremlin to become evil?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eating after midnight"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What changed in 1752 which caused Britain to have a White Christmas less frequently thereafter?", "answer":0, "answers":["The calendar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Chinese dynasty was overthrown in 1911", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Chinese dynasty was overthrown in 1911?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Christian holiday is celebrated immediately after Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["All Saints Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Christmas delicacy has blue veins running through it and tastes cheesy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stilton Cheese"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Christmas item was first introduced by Henry Cole in 1843", "answer":0, "answers":["The Christmas Card"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Christmas Item Was Invented By Liondon Bakery And wedding Cake Specialist 'Tom Smith' In 1847", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Crackers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Christmas item was invented by London baker and wedding-cake specialist Tom Smith in 1847?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas cracker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What city holds the distinction of opening the world's first public library in 1747?", "answer":0, "answers":["Warsaw, Poland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What city was destroyed by little boy", "answer":0, "answers":["Hiroshima"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What city was founded in 753 BC ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rome"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What city was john f. kennedy nominated for president in", "answer":0, "answers":["Los angeles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Colour Are Holly Berries", "answer":0, "answers":["Red"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Colour Are The Berries Of The Mistletoe Plant", "answer":0, "answers":["White"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What colour is Santa Claus' belt?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What colour is Santa Claus's belt?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What colour was added to the French flag during the French revolution?", "answer":0, "answers":["White"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What colour was Diana Spencer's engagement photograph suit?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blue"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What colour was Rudolph the Reindeer's nose?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What company made PacMan?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bally Midway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What company made the first color arcade game?", "answer":0, "answers":["Atari"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What company used the little aligators as it's symbol on clothing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Izods"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What computer game featured a disco leftover looking for love?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leisure Suit Larry"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Connects Kenny, Everett, Annie Lennox, And Sir Isaac Newton", "answer":0, "answers":["Born On Xmas Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Connects Richard Nixon, Lyndon B Johnson, Hubert Humphrey & Spiro Agnew", "answer":0, "answers":["4 US Vice Presidents During The 60's"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What contribution to our Christmas heritage did Ralph E. Morris make in 1895?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Lights"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country did Abel Tasman discover in 1642 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country did poinsettias originally come from? (Mexico,Us, Spain ,Brazil)", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country did the allies invade in world war ii's operation avalanche", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Country Is Dracula Said To Come From", "answer":0, "answers":["Transylvania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country is Men Without Hats originally from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country is poinsettia native to?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country produced the world's first Christmas postage stamp, and when?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country started the tradition of exchanging gifts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italy (Romans)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country was formerly known as Siam?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thailand"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What country was ruled by Pol Pot, leader of the Khmer Rouge party?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cambodia (Kampuchea)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What cult-fav eighties movie features John Lithgow from another dimension?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What date is St Stephen's Day?", "answer":0, "answers":["26th December"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What date is st. patrick's day", "answer":0, "answers":["March 17th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What daughter of czar nicholas ii is said to have escaped death in the russian revolution", "answer":0, "answers":["Anastasia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did 'DMZ' stand for in the vietnam war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Demilitarized Zone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did 'My True Love'' give to me on the eight day of Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight Maids-a-milking"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did 18 British Museums & Art Galleries Start To Do In 1974", "answer":0, "answers":["Charge Admission"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did a shepherd boy discover at qumram, jordon in 1947", "answer":0, "answers":["The dead sea scrolls"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Anne Boleyn have three of?", "answer":0, "answers":["Breasts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did British Honduras change its name to in 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["Belize"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did British Troops Destroy In Washington DC In 1814", "answer":0, "answers":["The President's House"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did David Stirling found?", "answer":0, "answers":["SAS"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Ed Peterson invent?", "answer":0, "answers":["Egg Mcmuffin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Eli Whitney invent?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cotton gin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Erik Rotheim invent in 1926?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aerosol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Francis Crick and James Watson build a molecular model of in 1953?", "answer":0, "answers":["DNA"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did Frenchman Andre Turcat Do On 2nd March 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Flew Concordes Maiden Voyage"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did Frosty The Snow man Have For A nose (Carrot, Button,Cherry,Coal)", "answer":0, "answers":["Button"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Harry Potter get for Christmas in his first semester at Hogwarts School?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Invisibility Cloak"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Henry Shrapnel invent?", "answer":0, "answers":["The exploding shell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did jack the ripper sign on his first note", "answer":0, "answers":["Yours truly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Julius Caesar cross to signal a revolt against the senate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubikon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did Lord Carnavon & Howard Carter vDiscover In 1922", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tomb Of Tutankhamen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Louis Cartier invent?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wristwatch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Marie Curie die of on 4th July, 1934?", "answer":0, "answers":["Radiation poisoning"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Napoleon have built to commemorate his victories?", "answer":0, "answers":["Arc de Triomphe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did New Zealand Vote To Abolish In 1961", "answer":0, "answers":["The Death Penalty"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Pennsylvania legalise before any other colony?", "answer":0, "answers":["Witchcraft"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Peter Minuit buy in 1626 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manhattan Island"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did pre-Christian pagans call Xmas time", "answer":0, "answers":["Yule"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did President J. Buchanan not have", "answer":0, "answers":["A wife"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did President J. Buchanan not have?", "answer":0, "answers":["A wife"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did presidents Madison, Monroe, Polk, and Garfield have in common", "answer":0, "answers":["The first name \" james \""], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did presidents Madison, Monroe, Polk, and Garfield have in common?", "answer":0, "answers":["The first name \"James\""], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Regan due to the striking air traffic controllers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fired them"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Rudolph never get to join in", "answer":0, "answers":["All the other reindeer games"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Sir Howard Carter discover in 1922?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tutankhamens Tomb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Temujin change his name to ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Genghis Khan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Did The Bank Of England Issue For The First Time In 1791?", "answer":0, "answers":["Banknotes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did the license plate on the Delorean in Back To The Future spell out?", "answer":0, "answers":["OUTATIME"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did the person chained to wall in Goonies want?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baby Ruth candy bar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did the Romans call Scotland?", "answer":0, "answers":["Caledonia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did the Romans call Wales?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cambria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What did Victorian women bathe in to try to enlarge their breasts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Strawberries"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Disaster Hit London In 1666?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Great Fire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Do 99% Of Pumpkins End Up As", "answer":0, "answers":["Lanterns"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What do Care Bears do when fighting enemies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stare"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What do historians call the journey made by Mao to the Northwest of China after Chiang Kai-Shek had driven his forces out of the South and East?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Long March"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What do Karen, Richard and Joseph all have in common", "answer":0, "answers":["All Carpenters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What do the five rings on the Olympic flag represent", "answer":0, "answers":["5 Continents"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What do the Irish call a spirit whose wailing signals imminent death", "answer":0, "answers":["Banshee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What does ALF stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alien Life Form"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What does Beetlejuice eat when he reaches out of his grave in the scale model of the town?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Fly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What does Dorothy have to steal from the wicked witch in oz", "answer":0, "answers":["Her Broomstick"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Does Dracula Actually Mean", "answer":0, "answers":["Son Of The Devil Or Son Of A Dragon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What does LL Cool J.'s name stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ladies Love Cool James"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What does the name Dracula mean in Romanian", "answer":0, "answers":["Son of the Devil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What duo lost their Grammy for Best New Artist from the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Milli Vanilli"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What eighties TV show starred Bruce Willis in a detective agency?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moonlighting"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What eighties TV show starred Tom Hanks in women's clothing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bosom Buddies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What employment did patricia hearst claim when booked", "answer":0, "answers":["Urban terrorist"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What energetic singer married the 13 year old daughter of his bass player?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jerry Lee Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What English city was known to the Romans as Venta Bulgarum?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winchester"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Event Killed On In Four People In Europe In The Fourteenth Century?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Black Death Or Bubonic Plague"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Family Live At 1313 Cemetary Lane", "answer":0, "answers":["The Adams Family"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What famous artist could write with both his left and right hand at the same time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leonardo da Vinci"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jarrow March"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What famous soap opera duo reigned on General Hospital in the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Luke and Laura"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What father/daughter duo made 'Gag Me With a Spoon' a household phrase during the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank & Moon Unit Zappa"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What fell into the pool in Caddyshack which caused a major exodus?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baby Ruth candy bar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What food was almost non-existent in Ireland in the 1840's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Potatoes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What french port did 200,000 british troops flee on june 4th 1940", "answer":0, "answers":["Dunkirk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What group landed in America in 1620", "answer":0, "answers":["The pilgrim s"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What group landed in America in 1620?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pilgrims"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What happened at 2:56 on the 21st July 1969 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["First Manned moon landing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Happened At Max Yasgur's Dairy Farm In New York State During 15-17th August 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Woodstock Festival"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Happened If You Looked A Gorgon In The Eye?", "answer":0, "answers":["You Turned To Stone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Happened To Alaska In 1867?", "answer":0, "answers":["It Was Sold By Russia To The United States"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Happened To The Apollo I Spacecraft On 27 January 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Caught Fire On Launch Pad Killing All 3 Crew"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What historic event does the nursery rhyme (Ring-a-ring of roses) commemorate?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Great Plague"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Hugely Successful Chain Of Stores First Opened It's Doors In 1954 In California", "answer":0, "answers":["McDonalds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is A Male Witch Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Warlock"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is a witches broom called", "answer":0, "answers":["A Besom"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is a Witches Familiar", "answer":0, "answers":["A Black Cat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is an assembly of witches called", "answer":0, "answers":["A Coven"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is Bob Dylan's Real Name", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Zimmerman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is Myrrh? Is it a herb, a gum resin or an essence distilled from orchids", "answer":0, "answers":["Gum resin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is New Year's Eve called in Scotland?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hogmanay"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is New Years Eve Caled It Scotland", "answer":0, "answers":["Hogmany"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the 15' by 18' cell that 146 captured british officers were forced into by indian troops in the 19th century called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black Hole of Calcutta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the all-time best-selling Christmas recording? (White Xmas, Jingle Bells, Frosty The Snowman, Rudolph the Red Nose Reindeer)", "answer":0, "answers":["White Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the collective name for a group of Angels", "answer":0, "answers":["A Host Of Angels"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the common name for cercis canadensis, the state tree of oklahoma", "answer":0, "answers":["Redbud"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the common name for muscivora forficata, the state bird of oklahoma", "answer":0, "answers":["Scissor-tailed flycatcher"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the English title of the carol written in 1818 by Austrian priest Josef Mohr originally called Stille Nacht?", "answer":0, "answers":["Silent Night"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the fear of Halloween called is it A Samhainophobia B Hallowphobia or is it C Druiphobia", "answer":0, "answers":["Samhainophobia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the first ghost seen by Ebenezer Scrooge in 'A Christmas Carol''", "answer":0, "answers":["His ex-partner Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the former name of Sri Lanka?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ceylon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the more common name for the plant Viscum Album?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mistletoe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the most popular Halloween decoration", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack-o-Lantern"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name for a noisy ghost or spirit", "answer":0, "answers":["Poltergeist"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Given To A Group Of Witches", "answer":0, "answers":["A Coven"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of David Hasslehoff's Talking car in the show 'Knight Rider'?", "answer":0, "answers":["KITT"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the 'big con'' that Paul Newman and Robert Redford carry out in _The Sting_?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Bad Guy In The Friday The 13th Series", "answer":0, "answers":["Jason"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Bad Guy In The Movie Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Myers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Cake Traditionally Eaten In Italy At Christmas Time", "answer":0, "answers":["Panettone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the cake traditionally eaten in Italy at Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Panettone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the German Officer who lived and died in Madrid and rescued Mussolini?", "answer":0, "answers":["Otto Skorzeny"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the lead singer for the Smiths?", "answer":0, "answers":["Morrisey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the Russian Czar's daughter who might_or might not_have survived the Russian revolution", "answer":0, "answers":["Anastasia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the Russian Czar's daughter who might-or might not-have survived the Russian revolution?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anastasia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Serial Killer In The Film Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Myers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the summer camp in the Friday 13th movies", "answer":0, "answers":["Camp Crystal Lake"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Name Of The Summer Camp In The Friday The 13th Movies", "answer":0, "answers":["Camp Crystal Lake"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of the telescope that was placed in orbit in the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hubble"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the name of Tiny Tim's father in the story, 'A Christmas Carol'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Crachit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the next line 'Christmas is coming the goose is getting fat …''", "answer":0, "answers":["Please put a penny in the old mans hat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the nickname of oklahoma", "answer":0, "answers":["Sooner state"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the nickname of the ship's computer in the 1979 film _Alien_?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mother"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the only national spectator sport originating entirely in the united states", "answer":0, "answers":["Rodeos"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Original Name For Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["Samhain (pron) sow-en"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the popular name for little baked sausages wrapped in rashers of streaky bacon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pigs in blankets"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the Roman numeral for fifty", "answer":0, "answers":["L"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the Roman numeral for fifty?", "answer":0, "answers":["L"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Significance Of The 1976 Film 'To The Devil _____ A Daughter'", "answer":0, "answers":["Last Horror Film Made By Hammer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Star Sign Of A Person Born On Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["Capricorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the the state capital of oklahoma", "answer":0, "answers":["Oklahoma city"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is The Title Of The 1992 Belgian Film About A Crew Following The Expolits Of A Serial Killer", "answer":0, "answers":["Man Bites Dog"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the title of the 1992 Belgian film about a film crew following and documenting the exploits of a serial killer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Man bites dog"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the traditional dessert in England on December 25?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Pudding"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is the weight of the largest pumpkin in the world is it A 1046 lbs B 1246 lbs or is it C 1446 lbs", "answer":0, "answers":["C 1446 lbs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is Traditionally Supposed To Happen On Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["Witches Come Out"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Is Worn Around The Neck To Keep Vampires Away", "answer":0, "answers":["Garlic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What is Zimbabwe's President Robert Mugabe's middle name", "answer":0, "answers":["Gabriel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What kind of teeth did George Washington have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wooden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What late night news show became popular in the eighties after the Iranian Hostage takeover?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nightline"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What late night show replaced Tom Synder's show?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Letterman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Left Lisbon On May 28 th 1588 & Did Not Return Intact", "answer":0, "answers":["The Spanish Armada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What liqueur goes into making a 'snowball' cocktail?", "answer":0, "answers":["Advocaat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What made Michael Milken famous and rich?", "answer":0, "answers":["Junk Bonds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What made the crew sick in the movie Airplane?", "answer":0, "answers":["The fish"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Major Event Occured In Russia In 1917", "answer":0, "answers":["The Russian Revolution"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What missionary station was built by Albert Schweitzer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lambarene"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What mistake did Coca-Cola make in 1985?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Coke"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Model Of Children's Bicycle Had A Gear Shift On The Frame", "answer":0, "answers":["The Chopper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What movie featured Reece's Pieces as part of the story, because the director couldn't obtain the rights to use M&M's?", "answer":0, "answers":["E.T."], "source":""},
  {"question":"What name did the indians give the black soldiers that were fighting against them in the late 1800's", "answer":0, "answers":["Buffalo soldiers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What name was given to the Allied invasion of North Africa in 1942?", "answer":0, "answers":["Operation Torch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Name Was Given To The Practise Of Killing Every Tenth Man In A Mutinous Roman Cohort?", "answer":0, "answers":["Decimate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Nationality Was Hannibal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carthaginian"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What notorious event occurred on the 24th October 1929?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wall Street Crash or (Black Thursday)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What ocean was amelia earhart flying over when she disappeared", "answer":0, "answers":["The pacific"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Office Did Churchill Hold For The Longest Continous Period?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prime Minister"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Opened In 1955 in Anaheim, near Los Angeles, California.", "answer":0, "answers":["Disneyland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What organization was founded by the rev. jerry falwell", "answer":0, "answers":["Moral majority"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What particular gimmick was used in the 1958 film House of Wax", "answer":0, "answers":["It was made in 3D"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What percentage of pumpkins grown are used on halloween is it A 97% B 98% or is it C 99%", "answer":0, "answers":["C 99%"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What period is also known as the age of fish?", "answer":0, "answers":["Devonian period"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What planet was 'ALF' from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Melmac"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What pope died 33 days after his election", "answer":0, "answers":["John paul i"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What popular US TV sitcom With 3 Words made its first appearance in 1951 & ran until 1957", "answer":0, "answers":["I Love Lucy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What pre-tv radio show turned film caused people to commit suicide when it was first aired?", "answer":0, "answers":["War Of The Worlds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Process Is Used For Dating Ancient Organic Objects?", "answer":0, "answers":["Radio Carbon Dating"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What product was the first TV advert advertising ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Toothpaste"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What purged the Great Plague of London ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Great Fire of London"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Reference Book Went On Sale For The First Time In 1955", "answer":0, "answers":["Guinness Book Of Records"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What region is the world's largest exporter of Christmas trees?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nova Scotia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What revelation did alexander butterfield make to the senate watergate committee", "answer":0, "answers":["The oval office bugging"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What rock magazine that came out in the eighties is now Rolling Stone's major competitor?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Saint's Day is celebrated on 26th December", "answer":0, "answers":["St. Stephen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Scary Movie Takes Place At The Overlook Hotel", "answer":0, "answers":["The Shining"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What seasonal name was given to Bart Simpson's dog", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa's Little Helper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Shakespearean king was actually king of Scotland for 17 years?", "answer":0, "answers":["Macbeth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What show did the catch phrase, 'Yeah, That's The Ticket' originate on?", "answer":0, "answers":["Saturday Night Live"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What show featured Nell Carter as a larger than life housekeeper?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gimme a Break"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What show was 'Whatcha talkin' 'bout Willis?' a standard catch phrase?", "answer":0, "answers":["Different Strokes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What snack food was portrayed in claymation dancing to 'Heard it Through the Grapevine'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raisins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Song Was Christmas Number One In The UK In Both 1975 And 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemian Rhapsody By Queen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What song, popular in the First World War, was written by George and Felix Powell?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pack up your Troubles in your Old Kit Bag"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What sort weapon was used in The Shining", "answer":0, "answers":["An Axe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Space Rocket Was Destroyed During Ground Tests At Cape Canaveral In 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Apollo 1"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Star Sign Would You Be If Your Birthday Fell On Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["Capricorn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What started in 1849 when gold was discovered at sutter's mill", "answer":0, "answers":["The california gold rush"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What style of dancing was popularized with rap music?", "answer":0, "answers":["Break Dancing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Tax Was Levied Between 1695 & 1851?", "answer":0, "answers":["Window Tax"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What time does the train arrive in Hadleyville ? Clue. 'A mans gotta do what a mans gotta do'", "answer":0, "answers":["High Noon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What time of day is known as the 'Devils Dancing Hour'", "answer":0, "answers":["Midnight"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What time would you watch 'Late Night With David Letterman' on NBC?", "answer":0, "answers":["12:30-1:30"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Toy Still Hugely Popular Today First Went On Sale In 1959 Costing Just $3", "answer":0, "answers":["Barbie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What toy was in short supply for the 1983 Chirstmas season?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cabbage Patch Kid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What toy was released in 1957 creating an instant craze among children?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Hula Hoop"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What treaty, signed in 1713, ended the War of the Spanish Succession?", "answer":0, "answers":["Treaty of Utrecht"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What tree is mentioned in the Christmas song 'Twelve Days of Christmas' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Pear tree"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What TV show with married couples and family life appealed to those over the age of 29?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thirty something"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What two mountain ranges did hannibal and his elephants march through in 218 b.c", "answer":0, "answers":["The pyrenees and alps"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What two mountain ranges did hannibal and his elephants march through in 218 b.c.", "answer":0, "answers":["The pyrenees and alps"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of animal is a caribou?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Reindeer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Type Of Ghosts Are Known To Play Pranks On Humans", "answer":0, "answers":["Poltergeists"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of men's jacket featured it's name on the outer breast pocket,and epaulets on the shoulders?", "answer":0, "answers":["Member's Only"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of natural disaster hit the American Midwest in 1935?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dust Storms"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of shoes did Run-D.M.C. sing about, which were what most rappers in the early eighties were into?", "answer":0, "answers":["Addidas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of shoes were favored by skateboarders? (Hint, it's 4 letterslong)", "answer":0, "answers":["Vans"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What type of sweet did Mars and Murrie develop in 1941?", "answer":0, "answers":["M & Ms"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What United States president was in office during the civil war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham Lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Venetian traveler and explorer landed in China and reached Kublai Khan's court in 1275?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marco Polo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What very Famous Link To Christmas Does Irving Berlin Have", "answer":0, "answers":["He Wrote White Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What volcano destroyed Pompeii", "answer":0, "answers":["Vesuvius"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What war followed the shot heard round the world", "answer":0, "answers":["The war of american independence"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What war lasted from June 5 to June 11, 1967?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six day war"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was A Ballista?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Ancient Siege Machine, A Giant Catapult Or Crossbow?"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was A Sopwith Camel?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Single Seater Armed Biplane Used In WWI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Alaska called before 1867?", "answer":0, "answers":["Russian America"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Alexander The Great's wife's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roxana"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Anne Frank Famous For?", "answer":0, "answers":["Writing A Diary About Her Hide From The Germans In WW2"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Baron Manfred Von Richthofen Also Known As?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Red Baron"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Brenda Lee doing Around The Christmas tree in 1958", "answer":0, "answers":["Rocking"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Charlie Rich Looking For In The 1970's", "answer":0, "answers":["The Most Beautiful Girl In The World"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Deciphed As A Result Of The Discovery Of The Rosetta Stone?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hieroglyphics"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was E.T.'s favorite candy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Recee's Pieces"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Elvis Presley's first motion picture?", "answer":0, "answers":["Love Me Tender"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Europe's first super-high-speed passenger train powered by?", "answer":0, "answers":["Electricity"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was first worn on the 10th October 1886 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tuxedo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Formerly Called Stingray Harbour?", "answer":0, "answers":["Botany Bay"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Founded In The Reign Of Henry VIII For The Protection Of The Royal Person?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yeoman Of The Guard Or Beefeaters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Gary Gnu's catch phrase?", "answer":0, "answers":["No Gnus is Good Gnus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was George A Custer's horses' name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Comanche"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Introduced Into The UK First, The Christmas Card Or The Christmas Tree", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Cards"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was ITV's live pop music show called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ready Steady Cook"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Jackie Kennedy's Name Before She Married John F Kennedy", "answer":0, "answers":["Jackie Onnasis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Joseph's job?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carpenter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Julie Christie's Home Town A=Bradford, B= Birmingham, C=Bath", "answer":0, "answers":["B= Birmingham"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was King Arthur's mother's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Igraine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was Launched In 1960 & Was Closely Linked With The Sexual Attitudes Of The Swinging 60's", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Maggie Seaver's maiden name on Growing Pains?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maggie Malone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was marco polo's home town", "answer":0, "answers":["Venice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Marilyn Monroe's last film?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Misfits"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Max Headroom's network number", "answer":0, "answers":["23"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was name of the Titanic's sister ship?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lucitania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was named after Amerigo Vespucci?", "answer":0, "answers":["America"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Operation Sea Lion in WWII?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Invasion of Britian"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was rudolf hess' sentence at the nuremburg trials", "answer":0, "answers":["Life Imprisonment"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Russian America called after 1867?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alaska"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was significant about the words (Watson, please come here, I want you) when spoken in 1876?", "answer":0, "answers":["First Complete Sentance Spoken On The Phone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was Thailand formerly known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Siam"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The 9th Century Tax Levied To Fight The Vikings?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dane Geld"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the board game introduced in the eighties which featured six categories of questions and little pie shaped pieces you had to collect?", "answer":0, "answers":["Trivia Pursuit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the capital of East Germany?", "answer":0, "answers":["East Berlin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the challanging method of catching a fly in Karate Kid?", "answer":0, "answers":["Using chopsticks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Colonial Name Of Ghana", "answer":0, "answers":["Gold Coast"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Contribution Of Actress Mercedes McCambridge To Linda Blairs Performance In The Excorcist", "answer":0, "answers":["Provided The Devils Voice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the contribution of actress Mercedes Mccambridge to Linda Blairs performance in The Exorcist", "answer":0, "answers":["She provided the devils voice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Coronation Year Of Queen Elizabeth 2nd", "answer":0, "answers":["1952"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the D-Day invasion password?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mickey Mouse"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the destination of the ship 'Mary Celeste' on it's final voyage November 1872, where it should never arrive ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Genoa"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Duchess Of Windsor's Name Before She Married The Duke?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wallace Simpson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was The Eldest Son Of Edward III Better Known As?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Black Prince"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the fight between Argentina and Great Britan over?", "answer":0, "answers":["Falkland Islands"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first American colony to legalise witchcraft?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pennsylvania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first fighting vehicle?", "answer":0, "answers":["War chariot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first game show on Mtv?", "answer":0, "answers":["Remote Control"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first movie Disney released through a subsidary company that carried an R rating?", "answer":0, "answers":["Down and Out In Beverly Hills"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first name of the baby girl who fell down the well?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jessica"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first newspaper produced in the United States ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Publick Occurences"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first postage stamp ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Penny Black"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first product to have a barcode?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrigley's gum"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The First Reich?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Holy Roman Empire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first ship to reach the Titanic after it sank?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carpathia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the first transatlantic radio message sent ?", "answer":0, "answers":["S"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Function Of Press Gangs In The Early Nineteenth Century?", "answer":0, "answers":["To Press Or Recruit Men Into The Royal Navy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the gift from the gods in the movie The Gods Must Be Crazy?", "answer":0, "answers":["A coke bottle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Given To The Period From 1919 To 1933 When Alcohol Was Banned In America", "answer":0, "answers":["The Prohibition"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Goverment Of Oliver Cromwell Called?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Commenwealth Goverment"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the inexpensive designer watch of choice amongst teenagers during the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Swatch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the initial capital of USSR?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leningrad"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the instrument of execution during the \"Reign of Terror\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Guillotine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the instrument of execution during the \"Reign of Terror\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Guillotine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the last chinese dynasty?", "answer":0, "answers":["Manchu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the last Port of call for the Titanic?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queenstown"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the leading cause of death in the late 19th century?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tuberculosis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the maiden name of Wallis Simpson, for whom Edward VIII abdicated in 1936?", "answer":0, "answers":["Warfield"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Most Common Present Girls Above The Age Of 16 Have Asked For in 2008", "answer":0, "answers":["A Boob Job"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the most Eastern country in Alexander The Great's command at his peak?", "answer":0, "answers":["India"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name (4 letters) of the New York night club that helped launch the career of several early new wave groups?", "answer":0, "answers":["CBGB's"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Given To Textile Workers Who Opposed Modernisation During The Nineteenth Century?", "answer":0, "answers":["Luddites"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name given to the atom bomb that was dropped on Hiroshima?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fat Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Given To The Coding Machine Used By The Germans In World War II?", "answer":0, "answers":["Enigma"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Given To The French Goverment Which Collaborated With The Nazis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vichy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Given To Those Who Campaigned For Social Reform In England Between 1836 & 1858?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Chartists"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Charles Lindbergh's plane in which he completed the first non-stop solo trans-Atlantic flight?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spirit of St Louis (achieved in 1927)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of David Hasselhoff's talking car in Knight Ridder?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kitt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of Dustin Hoffman's Character In The 1967 Film The Graduate", "answer":0, "answers":["Ben Braddock"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Eddie Murphy's character in Beverly Hills Cop?", "answer":0, "answers":["Axel Foley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Elizabeth Taylor's character in 'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret Pollitt 'Maggie the Cat''"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Garfield's vet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Liz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Grotbags the witches pet in the TV show 'Emu's World'", "answer":0, "answers":["Croc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Norm's wife on Cheers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vera"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Plato's school", "answer":0, "answers":["Academy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Plato's school?", "answer":0, "answers":["Academy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Punky Brewster's dog", "answer":0, "answers":["Brandon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of Scotland's First King?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenneth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of Spandau's only prisoner", "answer":0, "answers":["Leslie Joseph"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The 1971 TV Show In Which Adam Faith Played Ronald Bird", "answer":0, "answers":["Budgie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the B_29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb", "answer":0, "answers":["Enola gay"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the B-29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb?", "answer":0, "answers":["Enola Gay"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the balloon three americans piloted across the atlantic in 1978", "answer":0, "answers":["The double eagle ii"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the character on the 1st Garbage Pail Kids Pack?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blasted Billy or Adam Bomb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The Character Played By Anne Bancroft In The 1967 Film 'The Graduate''", "answer":0, "answers":["Mrs Robinson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the company that the characters on Taxi worked for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sunshine Cab Company"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the domestic videocassette tape recorder system introduced by Sony in 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["Betamax"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["Holiday Inn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the first ironclad warship ever launched?", "answer":0, "answers":["HMS Warrior"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the first nuclear powered submarine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nautilus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the government newspaper in ancient Rome ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Acat Diurna (Daily Happenings)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the host of Double Dare?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark Summers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the man who pioneered the above method of freezing food?", "answer":0, "answers":["Clarence Birdseye"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the multi-colored cube you had to re-organize?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rubik Cube"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The North Sea Oil Rig That Caught Fire In 1988", "answer":0, "answers":["Piper Alpha"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the nuclear missle defense system Reagan proposed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Star Wars"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the pandemic which killed over 1% of the world's population in 1918?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spanish Flu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the paperboy whose 1978 murder sparked a massive manhunt by British police?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Bridgewater"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the party dog that that was Budwiser's mascot in the late eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spuds McKenzie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the rich boy that Andie was asked to go to the senior prom with in the movie 'Pretty in Pink'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blaine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the scandal that resulted in the resignation of president Nixon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Watergate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the show that featured Sniglets?", "answer":0, "answers":["Not Necessarily The News"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the society heiress who stole 8 million pounds worth of pictures in 1974 and was sentenced to 8 years in prison", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Bridget Rose Dugdale"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Was The Name Of The Son Of Cleopatra & Julius Caesar", "answer":0, "answers":["Caesarion"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the space shuttle that exploded?", "answer":0, "answers":["Challenger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the teenage showgirl who caused MP John Profumo to resign?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christine Keeler"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the vehicle in which Sir Malcom Campbell broke the 300 mph barrier in 1935?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bluebird"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the name of the witch in the tv show emu's world", "answer":0, "answers":["Grotbags"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nationality of Marco Polo ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italian"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nationality of the prisoners in the \"Black hole of Calcutta\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["British"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nationality of the prisoners in the \"Black hole of Calcutta\"", "answer":0, "answers":["British"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nationallity of Rasputin ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Russian"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nickname of Charlene Tilton, who played Lucy Ewing in Dallas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Poison Dwarf"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the nickname of President Duvalier of Haiti, who died in 1971?", "answer":0, "answers":["Papa Doc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the only state george mcgovern carried in the 1972 presidential election", "answer":0, "answers":["Massachusetts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the pen name of author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson", "answer":0, "answers":["Lewis Carrol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was The poem A night before christmas originally called (The Night Visitor, Santa Claus Is Coming To Town, A Visit From St Nicholas, A Christmas Visit)", "answer":0, "answers":["A Visit From St Nicholas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the predecessor of the United Nations ?", "answer":0, "answers":["League of Nations"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the rank of Mark Phillips when he was married to Princess Anne in 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lieutenant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the real name of Eric Morecambes partner", "answer":0, "answers":["Ernest Wiseman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the second carry on film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carry on Nurse"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the sister ship of the olympic", "answer":0, "answers":["The titanic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the third country to get the \"bomb\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Britain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the third country to get the \"bomb\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Britain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What was the war during Regan's first term that took place on an island in the carribean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Grenada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What were 'Little Boy' and 'Fat Man'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Atom Bombs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Were (Mulberries)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Floating Harbours Used On D-Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Were Frosty The Snowmans Final Words", "answer":0, "answers":["I'll Be Back Again Someday"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What were men conscripted to work down mines in World War Two usually known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bevin Boys"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What were the B-52's named after? (Hint, it's not a plane)", "answer":0, "answers":["Beehive"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What were the earliest tree ornaments?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apples & Fruit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Were The Six Farm Hands Arrested For Forming A Trade Union Better Known As?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tolpuddle Martyrs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What wonder stood 32m high in rhodes harbour?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colossus of Rhodes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Would You Traditionally 'Bob' For At A Halloween Party", "answer":0, "answers":["Apples"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What year did British Honduras become Belize?", "answer":0, "answers":["1973"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What Year Saw The Imposition Of Martial Law In Poland", "answer":0, "answers":["1918"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What year was Margaret Thatcher elected British Prime Minister?", "answer":0, "answers":["1979"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What year was NASA founded?", "answer":0, "answers":["1958"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What year was the great drought in Britain?", "answer":0, "answers":["1976"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's 'Stir-Up Sunday'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Day To Make Xmas Pudding"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's fidel castro's brother's name", "answer":0, "answers":["Raoul"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's the claim to fame of abraham zapruder", "answer":0, "answers":["He filmed john f. kennedy's assassination"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's the oldest college in the u.s.", "answer":0, "answers":["Harvard"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's the resting place of those buried at sea", "answer":0, "answers":["Davey jones's locker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"What's the resting place of those buried at sea?", "answer":0, "answers":["Davey Jones's Locker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whats the resting place of those buried at sea", "answer":0, "answers":["Davey jones locker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When And Over What Was The First British Referendum Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["1975, Membership Of The EEC"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When Are Werewolves Expected To Appear", "answer":0, "answers":["When There Is A Full Moon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When Cook Discovered The Hawaiian Islands What Did He Name Them?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sandwich Islands"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When did Christmas become a Federal holiday in the U.S.?", "answer":0, "answers":["1831"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When Did Napoleon Bonaparte Begin His Reign As Emperor Of France", "answer":0, "answers":["1804"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When Did The Storming Of The Bastille Take Place?", "answer":0, "answers":["July 14th, 1789"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When does Santa deliver presents?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When is the 'Feast of Stephen'?", "answer":0, "answers":["December 26th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When is the Feast of St. Nicholas? Dec 6th, Dec 18th, Dec 25th, Dec 27th", "answer":0, "answers":["Dec 6th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When the choctaw indians were moved to oklahoma,they brought their crack police force with them. what were they called", "answer":0, "answers":["Lighthorsemen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When The Conservative Party Were Known As Tories Who Were Their Chief Opponents?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Whigs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When was D-day?", "answer":0, "answers":["June 6th, 1944"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When was Julius Caesar murdered?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ides of March"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When Was The Abolition Of The Death Penalty Made Permanent In Great Britain", "answer":0, "answers":["1969"], "source":""},
  {"question":"When was the Greek alphabet first used?", "answer":0, "answers":["800 BC"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did 'The Mayflower' take the pilgrims?", "answer":0, "answers":["New World"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did Bill and Hilary Clinton switch on Christmas lights in 1995?", "answer":0, "answers":["Belfast, Northern Ireland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did Churchill, Roosevelt and Stalin meet in 1945?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yalta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did Gerald Durrell open his zoo in 1958?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jersey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did Guinevere retire to die?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amesbury"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Did Harold McMillan Make His Famous Winds Of Change Speech In 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Cape Town, South Africa"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Did King John Sign The Magna Carta?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruunymede"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Did Napoleon Bonaparte Die In Exile?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Helena"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the battle of Waterloo take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["Belgium"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the Bay Of Pigs take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cuba"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the bayonet originate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bayonne, France"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the Birkenhead sink?", "answer":0, "answers":["Danger Point"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the famous witch trials of New England take place", "answer":0, "answers":["Salem"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the first atomic bomb explode", "answer":0, "answers":["Trinity site, new mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620", "answer":0, "answers":["Southampton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the most famous encirclement of the Nazi troops during WWII take place?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stalingrad"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where did the real St. Nicholas live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where do bathers traditionally go for a swim in Hyde Park on Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["The Serpentine"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where does Santa Claus live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lapland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where does Santa land his sleigh?", "answer":0, "answers":["On The Roof"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where In Egypt Is The Tomb Of Tutankhamen", "answer":0, "answers":["Valley Of The Kings, Luxor"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where in the UK would you go to celebrate 'Uphelia'' shortly after Christmas", "answer":0, "answers":["Shetland Isles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where is the infamous Lubjanka prison?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moscow"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was A Famous (Tea Party) Held In 1773?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boston Tea Party"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was Napoleon Bonaparte Born?", "answer":0, "answers":["Corsica"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where was Napoleon defeated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Waterloo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where was Nelson mandela in prison?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robben Island"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where was the 1962 world's fair held", "answer":0, "answers":["Seattle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where was the big British pop festival held in 1969?", "answer":0, "answers":["The isle of wight"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was The German Fleet Scuppered At The End Of World War I?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scapa Flow"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was The Only British Prime Minister To Be Assassinated Killed?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Lobby Of The House Of Commons"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was The Roman's First Colony Based In England?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colchester"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where was the Rosetta stone found ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cairo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was The Royalist HQ During The English Civil War?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxford"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Was Thomas Becket Murdered?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canterbury Cathedral"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where were Anne Boleyn and Catherine Howard both executed?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tower Of London"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where were numerous French nuclear tests conducted?", "answer":0, "answers":["Muraroa Atoll"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crete"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where were the first books printed?", "answer":0, "answers":["China"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where were the Hanging Gardens?", "answer":0, "answers":["Babylon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Where Were The McDonalds Massacred By The Campbells And The English In 1692?", "answer":0, "answers":["Glencoe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 'following' word did Frederico Fellini coin and use for the first time in his film La dolce vita ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paparazzi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which (Age) Occured Between The Stone And The Iron Ages?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bronze Age"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which `Rocky Horror Picture Show' actor played Mocata in the 1967 film 'The Devil Rides Out'", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Gray"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1776 American Affirmation Asserted The Basic Rights Of All To (Life, Liberty & The Pursuit Of Happiness)", "answer":0, "answers":["American Declaration Of Independence"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1922 German Vampire Film Starred The Genuinely Scary Looking Max Schreck In The Title Role", "answer":0, "answers":["Nosferatu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1945 Ealing Film Is A Sequence Of Supernatural Stories Told By A Group Of People In A Country House", "answer":0, "answers":["Dead Of Night"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1950s films took place in Altair-4 2280", "answer":0, "answers":["The Forbidden Planet"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1950s films took place in Burma 1943", "answer":0, "answers":["The Bridge on the River Kwai"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1950s films took place in Chicago and Miami 1929", "answer":0, "answers":["Some Like it Hot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1950s films took place in Hawaii 1941", "answer":0, "answers":["From Here to Eternity"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1964 Movie Had The Alternative Title 'How I Learned To Stop Worrying & Love The Bomb''", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Strangelove"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1972 musical won eight Oscars ? 'divine decadence darling'", "answer":0, "answers":["Cabaret"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1976 Film Is About A Persecuted Schoolgirl With Psychokinetic Powers", "answer":0, "answers":["Carrie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1976 film starring John Travolta is about a persecuted schoolgirl with psychokinetic powers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carrie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1976 Movie features the character 'Travis Bickle''", "answer":0, "answers":["Taxi Driver"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1978 film starring Roger Moore, Richard Burton and Richard Harris, is a bout a group of British mercenaries in Central Africa", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wild Geese"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1988 film saw Bruce Willis battling against a group of terrorists that crudely interrupted a Christmas party", "answer":0, "answers":["Die Hard''"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1992 Film Starred Goldie Hawn & Meryl Streep As 2 Woman Going To Extraordinary Lengths To Preserve Their Looks", "answer":0, "answers":["Death Becomes Her"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1993 Disney Movie Starred Bette Midler As A Witch", "answer":0, "answers":["Hocus Pocus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 1996 TV Christmas special, saw two of the stars dress as Batman and Robin, for a fancy dress party", "answer":0, "answers":["Only Fools & Horses"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 20th century American icon died on Halloween After A Night Out At The Viper Rooms", "answer":0, "answers":["River Phoenix"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 20th century American icons died on Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["River Phoenix"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line ' I'll follow him around the Horn, and around the Norway Maelstrom, and around perditions flames'", "answer":0, "answers":["Moby Dick"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line ' This is war. This is not a game of cricket'.", "answer":0, "answers":["The Bridge on the River Kwai"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line 'Hey Stella!'", "answer":0, "answers":["A Streetcar Named Desire"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line 'I always get the fuzzy end of the lollipop'", "answer":0, "answers":["Some Like it Hot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line 'Tomorrow you'll be one of us'", "answer":0, "answers":["The Invasion of the Body Snatchers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 50's Movie features the Line 'We've become a race of peeping toms'", "answer":0, "answers":["Rear Window"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's hit started with the line 'The Taxman's Taken All My Dough''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kinks/Sunny Afternoon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's Movie features The Line back in your gilded cage Melanie Daniels", "answer":0, "answers":["The Birds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's Movie features The Line by right she should be taken out and hung for the cold blooded murder of the English tongue", "answer":0, "answers":["My Fair Lady"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's Movie features The Line he's very clean", "answer":0, "answers":["A Hard Days Night"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's Movie features The Line wise men and grocers, they weigh everything", "answer":0, "answers":["Zorba the Greek"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's Movie features The Line you wouldn't be able to do those awful things to me if I weren't still in this chair", "answer":0, "answers":["What ever happened to Baby Jane ?"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60's singing duo divorced after 11 years of marriage?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sonny and Cher"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60s film was based on the true 'life' story of Robert Stroud", "answer":0, "answers":["The Birdman of Alcatraz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60s film was the true story of Helen Keller", "answer":0, "answers":["The Miracle Worker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which 60s sex symbol was, in film at least, attacked by anti-bodies ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rachel Welch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Act Gave People Temporary Release From From Prison To Prevent Starvation?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Cat & Mouse Act"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Act Has Had More Christmas Number One Singles In The UK Than Any Other?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beatles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actor best known for his horror films, did the narration on Micheal Jackson's hit 'Thriller'", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincent Price"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actor from The Harry Potter Films Also starred in The Movie Dracula", "answer":0, "answers":["Gary Oldman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Actor Of The Silent Era Was Known As 'The Man Of A Thousand Faces'", "answer":0, "answers":["Lon Chaney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actor of the silent era was known as The Man of a Thousand Faces", "answer":0, "answers":["Lon Chaney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actor won an Oscar in 1955 for their role in the movie 'The King and I''", "answer":0, "answers":["Yul Brynner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actor, an archdeacon in the TV series all gas & gaiters died in January 1979?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robertson Hare"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actress caused a sensation by appearing naked in the opening scene of the 1957 film _And God Created Woman _directed by her then husband Roger Vadim", "answer":0, "answers":["Brigitte Bardot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Actress Played Emma Peel In The Avengers", "answer":0, "answers":["Diana Rigg"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Actress played Grotbags the witch in the TV show Emu's World", "answer":0, "answers":["Carol Lee Scott"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actress played the role of Samantha stevens in the tv show bewitched and for a bonus point who played her in the 1990 movie version", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth Montgomery & Nicole Kidman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actress played the same part in all 3 Scream movies", "answer":0, "answers":["Neve Campbell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Actress Starred As Columnist 'Jane Lucas'' In The TV Sitcom Agony", "answer":0, "answers":["Maureen Lipman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which actress starred in the movie The Grudge?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sarah Michelle Gellar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Aerosmith song was re-made by Run D.M.C.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walk this way"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which American Gangster was shot dead outside a Chicago cinema in July 1934?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Dillenger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which American Military Academt was established in 1802 on the Hudson river ?", "answer":0, "answers":["West Point"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which American President Was Assassinated In A Theatre?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham Lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Annual Event First Hit Our Screens On The 5 th February 1988", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Nose Day"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Apollo mission carried Neil Armstrong and his cohorts to the moon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apollo 11"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Apollo space mission put the first men on the moon ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apollo 11"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Architect Designed The Whitehouse", "answer":0, "answers":["James Hoban"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which artificial fiber was invented in 1938 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nylon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Australian cricketer, playing for New South Wales against Queensland, scored a then world record first-class innings of 452 not out?", "answer":0, "answers":["Donald Bradman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Axis Powers In World War II Fought With The Allies In World War I?", "answer":0, "answers":["Japan & Italy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Baltic seaport was the German rocket centre during WWII?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peenemunde"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which band had a 1977 summer No 1 hit with `So You Win Again'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hot Chocolate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Band Had A UK Christmas Number 1 With The Song 'Stay Another Day'", "answer":0, "answers":["East 17"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which band member was Boy George allegedly seeing in Culture Club during the 80's? (Just name instrument he plays)", "answer":0, "answers":["The Drummer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Band Turned Down A 1 Million Pound Offer To Play At The Shea stadium In 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beatles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Band Was Rod Stewart A Member Of Before Going Solo", "answer":0, "answers":["The Faces"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Band Were At The UK Christmas Number One Spot In December 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["Pink Floyd / Wall"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Band Were Dropped By Their Label EMI In 1978 On Grounds Of Unacceptable Behavior", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sex Pistols"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which bank holiday was first celebrated in Britain in 1978?", "answer":0, "answers":["1st May"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Belgian noble woman was sentenced to death for bathing in the blood of servant girls she had murdered in order to keep her young", "answer":0, "answers":["Countess Elizabeth Bathory"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which best selling American writer wrote and directed the sci-fi film Westworld ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Crichton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Bill Haley song, which featured in the 1954 film _The Blackboard Jungle_, became the U.K.'s first Rock and Roll number one", "answer":0, "answers":["Rock Around The Clock"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which black athelete's successes at the Berlin Olympics caused Hitler to storm out of the stadium?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jesse Owens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Bond film does the character Dr Christmas Jones feature", "answer":0, "answers":["The World Is not Enough"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British alternative band takes its name from a character in the film To Kill a Mockingbird ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Boo Radleys"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British city was named Deva by the Romans?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chester"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British coin ceased to be legal tender in 1960?", "answer":0, "answers":["Farthing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British Comedian Was At No.1 In The UK With The Song 'Tears''", "answer":0, "answers":["Ken Dodd"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which british comedian was the first man to appear on the cover of 'playboy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Sellers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British Crime Author And Dame Died In January 1976 Aged 85", "answer":0, "answers":["Agatha Christie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which British prime minister died in 1965 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Building In Berlin Was Burned Down In 1933?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Reichstag"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Card Appeared In The UK For The Very First Time In 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["American Express"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which chapter of the 'Phantasm' series was entitled 'Oblivion'", "answer":0, "answers":["Phantasm 4"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which character in a Disney cartoon, wanted to make a coat out of 101 Dalmatians", "answer":0, "answers":["Cruella Devil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which character of the 'Bloom County' comic strip ran for president even though he was dead at the time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill the Cat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Character On TV Has The Real Name Of Eddie Fitzgerald", "answer":0, "answers":["Cracker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Chinese Dynasty Lasted From 1368-1644?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ming"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas carol contains the lines 'O Tidings of Comfort and Joy", "answer":0, "answers":["God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas carol contains the lines 'O Tidings of Comfort and Joy''", "answer":0, "answers":["God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen''"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas carol includes the lyrics '___To save us all from Satan's power, when we were gone astray..'?", "answer":0, "answers":["God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas Carol, tells the tale of a 10th Century Duke of Bohemia", "answer":0, "answers":["Good King Wenceslas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Christmas song contains the line 'Oh, the weather outside is frightful, but the fire is so delightful''", "answer":0, "answers":["Let it Snow, Let it Snow, Let it Snow"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which city did Crocket and Tubbs spend most of their time in?", "answer":0, "answers":["Miami Vice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which City Did The Allies Liberate On August 25th 1944", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which city is believed to be the birthplace of Jesus of Nazareth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bethlehem"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which city was Axel Foley a cop in?", "answer":0, "answers":["Detroit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which City Was Engulfed In Lava From Mount Vesuvius In AD79?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pompeii"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which city, famous for its 'Christmas Market', is also Known as 'The Gingerbread Capital of the World'? (Geneva, Bucharest,Nurumberg,Prague)", "answer":0, "answers":["Nuremburg"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which classic 1946 Christmas film features the line 'Daddy, every-time a bell rings, an angel gets its wings''", "answer":0, "answers":["It's a Wonderful Life"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Classic Scary Movie Features The Line 'They're Here'", "answer":0, "answers":["Poltergeist"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Comedian Hit The Front Page Of The Sun On March 13 th 1986 For Allegedly Eating A Hamster", "answer":0, "answers":["Freddie Star"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Comedien started Writing For Private Eye Magazine Ensuring Its Success", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Cook"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which comedy trio made a 'Daft Noise For Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["The Goodies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which comic strip animal devised by Otto Mesmer first appeared in 1931?", "answer":0, "answers":["Felix the Cat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which computer manufacturer in 1984 advertised their new computer during the Super Bowl, and never re-used the commercial?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apple"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Coronation street character, played by Jean Alexander, made her last appearance on Christmas Day 1987", "answer":0, "answers":["Hilda Ogden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which corporation opened it's new headquarters in Portland Place, London in May 1932?", "answer":0, "answers":["The BBC"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country blew up a Greenpeace ship in New Zealand?", "answer":0, "answers":["France"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Country Celebrates 'The Day Of The Dead' Instead Of Halloween Which Includes The Traditionn Of Paassing A Live Person In A Coffin Through The Streets", "answer":0, "answers":["Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country did China invade on Christmas day 1950", "answer":0, "answers":["Tibet"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country did Idi Amin invade in 1978?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tanzania"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country did St Nicholas come from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country donates the Christmas tree in Trafalgar Square", "answer":0, "answers":["Norway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country has the oldest national flag ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Denmark"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Country Hosted The Summer Olympic Games In 1952 A= Germany, B=Finland, C=France", "answer":0, "answers":["B= Finland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country is the largest exporter of Christmas trees?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canada"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Country Owns Christmas Island", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country ruled Cambodia immediately before WWII?", "answer":0, "answers":["France"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country traditionally provides Britain with a Christmas tree for Trafalgar Square in London?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norway"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Country Was Awarded The George Cross For Civilian Bravery In 1942?", "answer":0, "answers":["Malta"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Country Was Divided Into North And South In 1954 after communists took control of government.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vietnam"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany (1891)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country was previously known as the Dutch East Indies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indonesia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country was split into two zones by the Yalta agreement?", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which country was the first to allow women to vote in 1893?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which county cricket ground can be found at St Johns Wood in London", "answer":0, "answers":["Lords"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Crime Did Sirhan Sirhan Say He Had No Knowledge Of But Was Later Executed For In 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Kennedy Assasination"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Dark Wizard Was Portrayed By Christopher Lee In Lord Of The Rings", "answer":0, "answers":["Saruman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Date On The Christian Calendar Marks The Epiphany, When Jesus, Mary And Joseph Met The Three Wise Men?", "answer":0, "answers":["January 6 th"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Directors Films Include, Shivers , Videodrome & The Fly", "answer":0, "answers":["David Cronenberg"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which directors films included Shivers, Videodrome and The Fly", "answer":0, "answers":["David Cronenberg"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which doctor offered good advice in When Youre In Love With A Beautiful Woman?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Hook"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which does Carrie's Mother Warn Her Will Happen If She Attends The Prom", "answer":0, "answers":["They are all going laugh at you"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which drug, later found to have devastating side effects, was launched in 1958 to help pregnant women overcome morning sickness", "answer":0, "answers":["Thalidomide"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which duo had a 1987 Christmas hit with a cover of the Elvis song 'Always On My Mind''", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pet Shop Boys"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Egyptian president ordered the seizure of the Suez Canal in 1956?", "answer":0, "answers":["President Nassar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which eighties album, that sold 20 million plus copies, featured Vincent Price", "answer":0, "answers":["Thriller"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which eighties cartoon ended with the phrase: 'And knowing is half the battle?'", "answer":0, "answers":["G.I.Joe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which eighties fashion accessory consisted of a saftey pin and small beads?", "answer":0, "answers":["Friendship pins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which eighties musician got sued by a music related company for using their name as part of his pseudonym?*", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Dolby"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which eighties sitcom featured Tom Hanks in drag on a regular basis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bosom Buddies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which emperor made his horse a senator?", "answer":0, "answers":["Caligula"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which enduring western made its television debut On Sep 12th 1959 and ran until Jan 17 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bonanza"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English daily newspaper became a tabloid in 1971?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Daily Mail"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English King issued the Magna Carta in 1215?", "answer":0, "answers":["King John"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English King was crowned on Christmas Day", "answer":0, "answers":["William the Conqueror (1066)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English King Was Given The Title Defender Of The Faith By Pope Leo X?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry VIII"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English Monarch used radio to start the tradition of The Christmas Broadcast", "answer":0, "answers":["George V (1932)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which English Silver Coin, Worth Four Pennies, Was Taken Out Of Circulation In The 17th Century?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Groat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which entertainer famous for the one liner 'My Little Chickadee'' died on Christmas Day 1946", "answer":0, "answers":["W.C. Fields"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which European Country Withdrew Its Forces From NATO In 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greece"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Family Live At 1313 Mockingbird Lane, Mockingbird Heights", "answer":0, "answers":["The Munsters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous actor is honored in a statue in Leicester Square?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Chaplin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous Arab / Israeli war took place in 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yom Kippur war"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Famous Artist Was Shot And Wounded By Valeria Solanis In 1968", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Warhol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous explorer visited Australia and New Zealand, then surveyed the Pacific coast of North America?", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain George Vancouver"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Famous Female Solo Artist Was Born On Christmas Day 1971", "answer":0, "answers":["Dido"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous Giant Panda died at London Zoo in 1972?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chi Chi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous halloween party game originated from a custom to establish who would get married first", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobbing for apples."], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Famous Horror Actor Provided The Narration to Michael Jacksons Song & Short Mobie 'Thriller'", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincent Price"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous horror film featured a killer wearing a mask which was actually a Captain Kirk mask painted white", "answer":0, "answers":["Halloween"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous mathematician and astronomer was born on Christmas day in 1642", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Isaac Newton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Famous Person Of Film And TV Wrote The Autobiography Tall Dark And Gruesome", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher Lee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous ship sank in 1912 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Titanic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which famous Tapestry Commemorates The Conquering Of England?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bayeux Tapestry"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Famous Venetian Merchant Travelled To China And Worked For Kublai Khan?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marco Polo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which fellow singer was Roberta Flack paying tribute to in her song 'Killing Me Softly", "answer":0, "answers":["Don McLean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which fictional character created by Steve Coogan, is a presenter for Radio Norwich", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Partridge"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Fictional Radio Character Worked For Radio Norwich", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Partidge"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Film First Featured A Character Called Pinhead", "answer":0, "answers":["Hellraiser"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which film first featured a character later named Pinhead", "answer":0, "answers":["Hellraiser"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Food Of The Gods Was Said To Give Humans Immortality?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ambrosia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Football Team Became The First To Win The European Cup Winners Cup In 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Tottenham (Spurs)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Footballer Was Sent home From The 1978 Football World Cup For Taking Illegal Substances", "answer":0, "answers":["Willie Johnston"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Form Of Transport Was Used For The First Time By The British Police In 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Helicopters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which former British prime minister returned to power in 1951?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which former dictator was executed by firing squad on Christmas Day 1999", "answer":0, "answers":["Nicolae Ceausescu, (Romania)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which former Labour MP formed the New Party in 1931?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Oswald Mosley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Founder Of The Organisation For Afro American Unity Was Murdered In Harlem On 21 February 1965", "answer":0, "answers":["Malcolm X"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which French king was known as the Sun King ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis XIV"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which French Port Belonged To England Between 1347 & 1558?", "answer":0, "answers":["Calais"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which French Ruler Was Finally Defeated In 1815", "answer":0, "answers":["Napoleon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which frontiersman died at the Alamo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Davy Crockett"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which gangster died on the 25th January 1947 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Al Capone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which geographical location was the first word spoken on the moon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Houston"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which German Grand Prix circuit was used for a Formula 1 race for the last time in 1976, when Niki Lauda was almost killed?", "answer":0, "answers":["N?rburgring"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Government Post Was Held By John Profumo At The Time Of The Affair Involving Christine Keeler", "answer":0, "answers":["Secretary Of State For War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which great American inventor died in October 1931?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Edison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which great ocean liner was launched in 1934?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Queen Mary"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which great Renaissance figure had the surname Buonarroti?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michelangelo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Group Had 3 Consecutive Christmas Number One's In 1996,1997,1998", "answer":0, "answers":["The Spice Girls"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Group Had A 60s Hit With The Song 'She's Not There''", "answer":0, "answers":["The Zombies"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which group had a Christmas No 1 with 'Lilly The Pink''", "answer":0, "answers":["The Scaffold"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which group had a one hit wonder with 'Book of Love''?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Monotones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which group had a UK No.1 in 1981 with The Song 'Ghost Town'", "answer":0, "answers":["The Specials"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which group released the album 'Dark Side of the Moon'", "answer":0, "answers":["Pink Floyd"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which groups first album was entitled 'Piper At the Gates Of Dawn''", "answer":0, "answers":["Pink Floyd"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which hero, a Christmas panto favourite, marries Bedr-El-Budar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aladdin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Hitchcock movie With One Word In It's Title was released in 1958?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vertigo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which horror film star was portrayed by Martin Landau in Tim Burtons 1994 film about cult film maker Ed Wood", "answer":0, "answers":["Bela Lugosi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Horror Film Star Was Portrayed In An Oscar Winning Performance By Martin Landau In Tim Burtons 1994 Film About Cult Filmaker Ed- Wood", "answer":0, "answers":["Bella Logosi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which horse won the 1964 Derby", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Claus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Household Cleaning Product What Launched At The Savoy Hotel In 1960 And By The 1970's Was Being Used In 6 Out Of 10 UK Households", "answer":0, "answers":["Fairy Liquid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which houses fought the War of the Roses?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lancaster and York"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Institution Was Founded By The Roman Catholic Church In The 13th Century To Root Out Heresay?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Inquisition"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Instrument Of Torture Had a Hinged Case Full Of Spikes?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Iron Maiden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which is the most ancient walled city?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jericho"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which is the name of the baddie in the Harry Potter series", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Voldemort"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which is the name of the killer in A Nightmare on Elm Street", "answer":0, "answers":["Freddy Krueger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which is the oldest University in the USA?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harvard (founded 1636, in Cambridge Massachusetts)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which island was Napoleon from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Corsica"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Islands In The Indian Ocean Gained Their Independence From Britain In 1976", "answer":0, "answers":["The Seychelles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which James Bond Film Featured A Bond Girl Called Doctor Christmas Jones", "answer":0, "answers":["The World Is Not Enough"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which James Bond Movie Is Set During The Christmas Period", "answer":0, "answers":["On Her Majestys Secret Service"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which King of France was known as the (Sun King)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis XIV"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which King Was Overthrown As A Result Of The French Revolution", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis XVI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which King Wore Two Shirts At His Execution So As Not To Shiver And Appear Frightened?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles I"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Lancashire Town Has A Name That Means A Small Brass Wind Instrument Used For Summoning Witches & Warlocks", "answer":0, "answers":["Oswaldtwistle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Lancs Town Has A Name That Means A Small Brass Wind Instrument Used For Summoning Witches & Warlocks", "answer":0, "answers":["Oswaldtwistle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Law Was Passed At The End Of The Eighteenth Century Making Trade Unions Illegal?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Combination Acts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which legendary American fire fighter was sent to extinguish the oilfields of Kuwait in 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Adair"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which London building was gutted by fire in November 1936?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Crystal Palace"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which London Theatre Referring To The 2nd World War Used The Slogan (We Are Never Closed)", "answer":0, "answers":["The Windmill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Long Running Sci Fi Program Was First Aired In November 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Who"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Magician Was An Advisor To King Arthur", "answer":0, "answers":["Merlin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which major international organization was created in 1945 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["United Nations"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Margaret Mitchell novel, later a successful film, won the 1937 Pulitzer Prize?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gone With The Wind"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which member of the Beatles got his first drum kit on Christmas Day 1957", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Michael Jackson song Was Christmas Number One In 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Earth Song"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which military battle took place in 1815", "answer":0, "answers":["Waterloo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which military battle took place in 1815?", "answer":0, "answers":["Waterloo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Mother & Daughter Both Appeared In John Carpenters Film The Fog", "answer":0, "answers":["Janet Leigh & Jamie Lee Curtis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which mother and daughter both appeared in John Carpenters The Fog", "answer":0, "answers":["Jamie Lee Curtis / Janet leigh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which movie had a device known as a flux-capacitor?", "answer":0, "answers":["Back to the Future"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which movie is the line 'Snakes, I hate snakes' from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raiders Of The Lost Ark"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which movie prompted the style of wearing cutoff sweatshirts over the shoulder?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flashdance"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Musical Opened On Broadway In 1956 And Starred Julie Andrews", "answer":0, "answers":["My Fair Lady"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Mutiny Took Place In 1789?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mutiny On The Bounty"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which name belongs rightfully to The Craft Is It Bonnie, Shelly, Sally, Penny", "answer":0, "answers":["Bonnie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which nation did Moshoeshoe found?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basotho"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which nation was led by Genghis Khan?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mongolia"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which new country was formed in 1971 at the end of the Pakistan / India conflict?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bangladesh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which notorious murderer, hanged in July 1953, had his story told in the film _Ten Rillington Place_", "answer":0, "answers":["John Reginald Christie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which novel opens and closes with the letters of Robert Walton", "answer":0, "answers":["Frankenstein"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which novel, published in1932, was a vision of the future as a sanitised society?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brave New World"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which nursery rhyme was the first gramophone recording?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Had A Little Lamb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of Courteney Coxs co-stars from the Scream films is now her husband", "answer":0, "answers":["David Arquette"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Of Courtney Cox's Co Stars From The Scream Films Is Now Her Husband", "answer":0, "answers":["David Arquette"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Of Hitler's Deputies Flew To Scotland In 1941?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rudolf Hess"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Of Santa's Reindeer Shares It's Name With A High Street Store", "answer":0, "answers":["Comet"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of Santa's reindeers shares its name with a mythological God of Love", "answer":0, "answers":["Cupid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Of Santas Reindeers Shares Its Name With A High Street Shop", "answer":0, "answers":["Comet"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of the following is a 1983 New Order song `Creepy', `Spooky' or `Scary'\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spooky"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of the following was not a gift from a magi? (Diamonds,Gold, Frankincense,Myrrh)", "answer":0, "answers":["Diamonds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of the Wise Men was said to have brought the gift of gold for the baby Jesus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Melchior"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of these is NOT one of Santa's reindeer? (Donner, Dixen, Comet, Dasher)", "answer":0, "answers":["Dixen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which of these women NEVER married Frank Sinatra? A= Mia Farrow, B= Ava Gardner, C= Lana Turner", "answer":0, "answers":["C = Lana Turner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Olympics did the US boycott?", "answer":0, "answers":["1980"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which pain relieving product was subjected to a public relations scare in the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tylenol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which period was first, jurassic or carboniferous?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carboniferous"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which pie originates from medieval Christmas time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Humble Pie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which poisonous concoction was Socrates given to drink to carry out his death sentence?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hemlock"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which police-dog was one of Stalin's favourites?", "answer":0, "answers":["Berya"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Political Party Rose To Power In China In 1949", "answer":0, "answers":["The Communists"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Pop Singer Married Maurice Gibb Of The Bee Gees In February Of 1969?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lulu"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which popular 60s film took place in and around 17 Cherry Tree Lane, London, in 1910 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Poppins"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which popular Christmas carol was originally a piece written by King Henry VIII? A= God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen, B= We 3 Kings Of Orient Are, C= What Child Is This, D=Good King Wenceslas", "answer":0, "answers":["C= What Child Is This"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Popular Christmas Movie Featured A Must Have Toy Called 'Turbo Man''", "answer":0, "answers":["Jingle All The Way"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which popular poem was alternatively known as A Visit from St Nicholas? '", "answer":0, "answers":["Twas The Night before Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which president was responsible for the 'Louisiana Purchase'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Jefferson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which president was responsible for the Louisiana Purchase", "answer":0, "answers":["Jefferson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which president was responsible for the Louisiana Purchase?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jefferson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Queen Had An Extra Finger?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Queen Of England Was Known As Bloody Mary?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary I"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which quirky brunette was one of the first MTv VJ's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martha Quinn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which racist organisation was formed in Tennessee in 1865?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ku Klux Klan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which re-released Queen anthem topped the Christmas charts in 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Bohemian Rhapsody"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which reindeer isn't mentioned in the poem 'The Night Before Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["Rudolph"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which religious group first celebrated what we've come to know as Halloween", "answer":0, "answers":["The Druids"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Revolution Began In 1789", "answer":0, "answers":["The French Revolution"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Revolutionary Icon Was Killed On 9th October 1967", "answer":0, "answers":["Che Guevara"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which river did George Washington cross on Christmas night in 1776 in the American Revolutionary War?", "answer":0, "answers":["Delaware"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which rock group of the eighties gave away a silver keychain at every concert, which was supposed to bring good luck to whoever caught it?", "answer":0, "answers":["ZZ Top"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which rock star died when the Mini car, driven by his girlfriend crashed into a tree?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marc Bolan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Roman Emperor Followed Claudius?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which royal couple were married on the 29th July 1981", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles and Diana"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Royal House Ruled England Between 1603 & 1714?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Stuarts"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Saint's Day is celebrated on Boxing Day", "answer":0, "answers":["St Stephen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Sci-Fi Sitcom star like to eat cats?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alf"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Scottish actor famously sang in the film Darby O Gill & the little people?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Series Of Films Features A Habitual Killer Called Michael Myers", "answer":0, "answers":["Halloween"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which series of films features a habitual serial killer called Michael Myers", "answer":0, "answers":["The Halloween series of films"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Series Of Horror Movies Were Greatly Influenced By A Painting By Norwegian Artist Edvard Munch", "answer":0, "answers":["Scream"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Shakespeare Play Begins With 3 Witches Upon The Heath", "answer":0, "answers":["Macbeth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which ship did Charles Darwin captain?", "answer":0, "answers":["HMS Beagle"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which shipbuilding company constructed the Titanic?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harland & Wolff"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which shop in Regent St is the largest toy store in the world", "answer":0, "answers":["Hamley's"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which silent film star was awarded a Knighthood in 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Chaplin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Singer Born On Christmas Day Released A Debut ASlbum Entitled No Angel", "answer":0, "answers":["Dido"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which singer sang 'I Believe In Father Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["I Believe In Father Christmas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Singer Starred In The Title Role Of The Film 'Merry Christmas Mr Lawrence''", "answer":0, "answers":["David Bowie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Singer Was 'Driving Home For Christmas'' In 1988", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Rea"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which singers Christmas favourite is having his `nuts roasting on an open fire___'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nat King Cole"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which singing family was David Cassidy a member of", "answer":0, "answers":["The Partridge Family"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which sitcom helped launch Michael J. Fox's career by portraying him as a money-grubbing teenager?", "answer":0, "answers":["Family Ties"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which slasher film series featured masked killer Michael Myers", "answer":0, "answers":["Halloween"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Small Car Did Austin And Morris Launch In 1959?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mini"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Song By James Blunt Released In March 2006 Failed To Enter The UK Top 20 Despite Being Top Of The Radio 1 Playlist For That Month", "answer":0, "answers":["Wisemen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which song was a Christmas No 1 in both 1975 and 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Queen's 'Bohemian Rhapsody"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which song was a UK chart hit for `The Goodies' in 1975?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Funky Gibbon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Spanish explorer first travelled to Jamaica?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher Columbus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Spanish King Sent An Armada Against England In 1588?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philip II"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Sport Is Governed By The Queensbury Rules", "answer":0, "answers":["Boxing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which State Became The 47th US State In 1912", "answer":0, "answers":["New Mexico"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which stormy couple had a hit with Nutbush City Limits?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ike & Tina Turner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Surrey cricketer made history at Old Trafford in 1956 when he took 19 wickets in the test match against Australia", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Laker"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which T - Rex hit contains the line 'Take a black cat and sit it on your shoulder'", "answer":0, "answers":["Ride A White Swan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which theatre, that `never closed', closed in the sixties for good?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Windmill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which token vegetable is often included in the ingredients of a Christmas pudding?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carrot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which toy, with a name meaning 'play well'' was launched by Danish toymakers Ole and Godtfred Kristiansen in 1958", "answer":0, "answers":["Lego"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which traditional song contains the lines 'He's making a list, He's checking it twice, Gonna find out whose naughty or nice''", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Claus Is Coming To Town"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which TV Character Owns A Talking Cat Called Salem", "answer":0, "answers":["Sabrina Teenage Witch"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which TV Family Adopted A Greyhound For Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Simpsons"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which TV show portrayed the lives of performing arts high school students", "answer":0, "answers":["Fame"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which two European leaders signed a non-aggression pact on 23 August 1939?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hitler & Stalin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which two words are inscribed on a Victoria Cross?", "answer":0, "answers":["For Valour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which type of British fighter plane shot down 1,294 enemy aircraft in World War One?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sopwith Camel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which type of vegetable went on sale in frozen form in Massachusetts in June 1930?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which U. S. President insisted on putting lit candles on the White House Christmas tree, even though it was a fire hazard? Calvin Collidge, Herbert Hoover, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Theodore Roosevelt,", "answer":0, "answers":["Franklin Delano Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which U.S. President _banned _ Christmas trees from the White House because he believed cutting them harmed the environment?", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which U.S. president said, \"The buck stops here\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Truman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which U.S. president said, \"The buck stops here\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Truman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which U.S. President was the first to have a Christmas tree in the White House?", "answer":0, "answers":["Franklin Pierce (1853-1857)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which US president said 'the buck stops here'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harry Truman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which US President Was Forced To Resign In 1974", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Nixon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which US Singer Duetted With Donna Summer On The US Number One 'No More Tears''", "answer":0, "answers":["Barbara Streisand"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oklahoma"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which vehicle designed by Ferdinand Porsche, went into mass production in 1936?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Volkswagen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Very Famous Horror Story Was Written By Gaston Leroux", "answer":0, "answers":["The Phantom Of the Opera"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Wall Did The Romans Build To Keep Out Marauding Scots?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hadrians Wall"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which war did the signing of an armistice on 27th July 1953 end?", "answer":0, "answers":["Korea"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which war drama was first seen on British Television in October 1972?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colditz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982", "answer":0, "answers":["The Falklands War"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which was the first Chinese dynasty?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shang"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which was the first magazine to publish a hologram on its cover?", "answer":0, "answers":["National Geographic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Was The First Town To Be Liberated By The Allies On D-Day?", "answer":0, "answers":["Caen"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which was the last of the 5 civilized tribe to arrive in oklahoma", "answer":0, "answers":["Seminole"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Was The Only Song To Spend 6 Weeks As a UK No.1 In 1979 It Also Featured In A 1978 Movie", "answer":0, "answers":["Bright Eyes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which was the sacred animal of ancient egypt", "answer":0, "answers":["Cat"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Well Known Actor Died On Christmas Day 1977", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Chaplin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Welsh actor won Christ's Robe in a dice game in The Robe?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Burton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which Wild West legend was born Henry McCarty?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy the Kid, alias William H Bonney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which witch did Ozzy Osborne sing about in 1980", "answer":0, "answers":["Aleister Crowley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which witch is credited in the Bible with raising the spirit of Samuel at the request of King Saul", "answer":0, "answers":["Witch of Endor"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which woman flew from England to Australia in 1930?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amy Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Which word, associated with Christmas comes from a Greek word meaning 'we can act anything''", "answer":0, "answers":["Pantomime"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who advocated planting peanuts and sweet potatoes to replace cotton and tobacco?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Washington Carver"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who appeared on the back of a US banknote in 1875?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pocahontas"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who are the four ghosts in Charles Dickens' A Christmas Carol?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christmas Past, Present, Yet to Come, and Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who as Lord Protector of England, banned Christmas in 1647", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Cromwell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who asked, Ever Fallen In Love?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Buzzcocks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who assassinated John Lennon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mark David Chapman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who assassinated president Kennedy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lee Harvey Oswald"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Assassinated Robert Kennedy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sirhan Bishara Sirhan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who banned Christmas in 1647", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Cromwell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who banned Christmas in England between 1647 and 1660?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Cromwell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Became Chancellor Of Germany In 1933", "answer":0, "answers":["Adolf Hitler"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Became premier of Cuba in 1959.", "answer":0, "answers":["Fidel Castro"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Became President Of France After Charles De Gaulle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Georges Pompidou"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who became president of South Africa in 1989?", "answer":0, "answers":["F.W. de Klerk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Brought Back Tobacco And Potatoes From The Americas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Walter Raleigh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who built Camelot?", "answer":0, "answers":["King Arthur"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who built the Lambarene missionary station?", "answer":0, "answers":["Albert Schweitzer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who built the Taj Mahal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shah Jahan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who burned Atlanta in 1864?", "answer":0, "answers":["General Sherman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who captained the HMS Beagle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Darwin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who caused outrage with the following quote 'We are more popular than Jesus now'' I don't know which will go first Rock n Roll or Christianity''", "answer":0, "answers":["John Lennon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Coined The Phrase 'Turn On Tune In, Drop Out''", "answer":0, "answers":["Timothy Leary"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Coined The Phrase (Goverment Of The People, By The People And For The People)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham Lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Commanded The Confederate Armies During The American Civil War?", "answer":0, "answers":["General Robert E.Lee"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who committed the first daytime robbery?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank and Jesse James"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who created an 86-letter syllabary for the cherokee language", "answer":0, "answers":["Sequoyah"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who denounced Stalin?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nikita"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Described Russia As (A Riddle Wrapped In A Mystery, Inside An Enigma)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who designed Regent's Park in London in 1811?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Nash"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who developed the first nuclear submarine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Soviet Union"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did David Bowie duet with on the Christmas Hit 'Little Drummer Boy''", "answer":0, "answers":["Bing Crosby"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did dita beard work for", "answer":0, "answers":["Itt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did Henry VIII marry when he was 18?", "answer":0, "answers":["Catharine of Aragon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did Squeaky Fromme try to assassinate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gerald Ford"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did the los angeles times endorse in the 1964 preisential election", "answer":0, "answers":["Barry goldwater"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did the singer Lulu marry in 1969?", "answer":0, "answers":["Maurice Gibb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who did Tom Cruise marry on Christmas Eve 1990", "answer":0, "answers":["Nicole Kidman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who died three days after Elvis Presley?", "answer":0, "answers":["Groucho Marx"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who died three days before Groucho Marx?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Directed Terence Stamp In His First Starring Role In The Film Billy Budd In 1962", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Ustinov"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who directed the 1946 classic 'It's A Wonderful Life''", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Capra"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Directed The 1968 Classic Horror Movie 'Rosemary's Baby''", "answer":0, "answers":["Roman Polanski"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Directed The 1968 Film Rosemary's Baby", "answer":0, "answers":["Roman Polanski"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who directed the 1968 film Rosemarys Baby", "answer":0, "answers":["Roman Polanski"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who directed the 1976 movie 'The Omen' - The first part of the omen trilogy", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Donner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who directed the movie 'An American in Paris?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincente Minnelli"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Directed The Original Halloween Movie", "answer":0, "answers":["John Carpenter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who discovered Christmas Island on Christmas Eve 1777", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Cook"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who discovered the Grand Canyon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Francisco Coronado"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who discovered the tomb of Tutankhamen?", "answer":0, "answers":["Howard Carter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who discovered the vaccination against smallpox in 1796?", "answer":0, "answers":["Edward Jenner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who does Jamie Lee Curtis play in 'Halloween 20 years later (H20)", "answer":0, "answers":["Kere Tate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who drafted most of the American Declaration of Independence?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Jefferson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Eastenders Character Left Albert Square On Christmas Day 2005", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfie Moon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who fiddled while Rome burned?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who first conceived the idea of a Christmas tree", "answer":0, "answers":["Prince Albert"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who fixed the date of the Christian festival 'Easter'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Council of Nicaea"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who forced 146 captured British officers into the Black Hole of Calcutta?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indian troops"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Formed The First Labour Goverment?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ramsey MacDonald 1924"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Founded The Open University?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harold Wilson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who founded the Salvation Army in London, 1865?", "answer":0, "answers":["William Booth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who gave john f. kennedy a dog named pushinka", "answer":0, "answers":["Nikita khrushchev"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who got slimmed first in Ghostbusters?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Venkman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who graced the cover of the 1st 'Playboy' in 1953? A=Sophia Loren, B=Marilyn Monroe, C= Lauren Baccall", "answer":0, "answers":["B = Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who had a 1970 No 1 with 'I Hear You Knockin'. ''", "answer":0, "answers":["Dave Edmunds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who had a Christmas No 1 with 'There's No-One Quite Like Grandma''", "answer":0, "answers":["St Winifred School Choir"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who had a hit with Schools Out in 1972?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alice Cooper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who had a hit with the smooth and soulful You To Me Are Everything ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Real Thing"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who had a Message To Rudy?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Specials"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Funky Cold Medina,'", "answer":0, "answers":["Tone Loc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Is There Something I Should Know'", "answer":0, "answers":["Duran Duran"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Kiss On My List',", "answer":0, "answers":["Hall and Oates"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Never Say Never,'", "answer":0, "answers":["Romeo Void"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Other Woman,'", "answer":0, "answers":["Ray Parker Jr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Paranomia,'", "answer":0, "answers":["Art of Noise feat Max Headroom"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Politics of Dancing',", "answer":0, "answers":["Re-Flex"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Queen of Hearts'", "answer":0, "answers":["Juice Newton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Rock 'n' Roll High School,'", "answer":0, "answers":["The Ramones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Two of Us,'", "answer":0, "answers":["Grover Washington with Bill Withers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who helps Santa make toys?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elves"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who imported the first Go set into Britain ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marco Polo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who in 1893 defined vegtables as plants eaten in a meal and fruits as plants eaten as dessert ?", "answer":0, "answers":["United States Supreme Court"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who In 1963 , Became The First Film Star To Earn A Million Dollars For A Single Film", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth Taylor In Cleopatra"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who in 1988 became the first elected female prime minister in an Islamic country ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Benazir Bhutto"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who in March 1958 became known by the number 53310761?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who introduced bagpipes to the British Isles?", "answer":0, "answers":["Romans"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who introduced Xmas trees to England in 1841", "answer":0, "answers":["Prince Albert"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented crop insurance?", "answer":0, "answers":["Benjamin Franklin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the aerosol?", "answer":0, "answers":["Erik Rotheim"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the ballpoint pen?", "answer":0, "answers":["Georgo and Laszlo Biro"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Invented The Christmas Cracker", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Smith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the cotton gin?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eli Whitney"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the exploding shell?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry Shrapnel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the gatling gun?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Gatling"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the record player ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Alva Edison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Invented The Spinning Frame In 1769?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Richard Arkwright"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the thermometer in 1593?", "answer":0, "answers":["Galileo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who invented the wristwatch?", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis Cartier"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is \"The Iron Lady\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret Thatcher"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is best remembered as the mistress of Lord Nelson?", "answer":0, "answers":["Emma Hamilton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is considered the father of medicine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hippocrates"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is famous for historically riding naked on horseback through Coventry, England ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lady Godiva"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is generally given credit for the term 'Rock and Roll?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Freed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is identified with the word 'eureka'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Archimedes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is known as the high priest of revenge?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philip Seldon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is known for his 'theory of evolution'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Darwin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is Prince Vladimir Tepes better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dracula"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is recognised as the father of geometry?", "answer":0, "answers":["Euclid"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Is The Father Of Queen Elizabeth 2nd", "answer":0, "answers":["George VI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is the first ghost seen by Scrooge in 'A Christmas Carol''", "answer":0, "answers":["Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Is The Only British Prime Minister To Have Been Assassinated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spencer Perceval, 1812"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who is the only one who understands John Shaft ?", "answer":0, "answers":["His woman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Is The Youngest Member Of The Rolling Stones", "answer":0, "answers":["Keith Richards"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who killed 5 london prostitutes in 1888", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack the ripper"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who killed Jesse James?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Ford"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who killed who in 1963 in what is generally regarded as the first live televised murder?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Ruby killed Lee Harvey Oswald"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Knocked Out Floyd Patterson To Win The World Heavyweight Boxing Title In 1962", "answer":0, "answers":["Sonny Liston"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Lead The British Labour Party Before Harold Wilson?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Gaitskell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Jones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Led A 125 Mile March Of Child Worker To Theodore Roosevelt's Vacation Home On Long Island", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Harris Jones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who led the attack on the Alamo", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa anna"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who led the attack on the Alamo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Santa Ana"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who led the children of Israel out of Egypt?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moses"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who led the mongols?", "answer":0, "answers":["Genghis Khan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Made The First Non-Stop Transatlantic Crossing In An Aeroplane?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alcock & Brown"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who married actress Nancy Davis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronald Reagan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who met in Yalta in 1945 (in alphabetical order)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Churchill Roosevelt Stalin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Moved Into His Factory On New Yorks East 47th Street In 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Warhol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who ordered the persecution of the Christians in which Peter and Paul died?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nero"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who outlawed gladiator sports in Rome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who penned the words, 'Hubble, bubble toil and trouble, fire burn and cauldron bubble'", "answer":0, "answers":["William Shakespeare"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Pioneered Nursing Whilst Serving In The Crimean War?", "answer":0, "answers":["Florence Nightingale"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Placed His Cloak On A Puddle For Elizabeth I?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Walter Raleigh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played an elf called Patch in the film 'Santa Claus the Movie''", "answer":0, "answers":["Dudley Moore"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played Bowls Before Engaging The Spanish Armada?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Francis Drake"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played George III in Beau Brummell? (Robert Morely, Alec Guiness, Cardew Robinson)", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Morely"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played Jack Nicholson's Wife In The Shining", "answer":0, "answers":["Shelley Duvall"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played Jack Nicholsons wife in The Shining", "answer":0, "answers":["Shelley Duvall"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played Norman Bates in the 1998 remake of 'Psycho'", "answer":0, "answers":["Vince Vaughn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the first screen incarnation of Dr. Hannibal Lecter", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Cox"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the lead role in the 1960 Hammer production The Curse of the Werewolf", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Reed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the monster in the 1931 film Frankenstein", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Karloff"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the policeman in The Blue Lamp?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Warner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played The Role Of Flick In The Tv Soap Neighbours", "answer":0, "answers":["Holly Valance"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the Spirit of Christmas in the 1988 TV film 'Blackadder's Christmas Carol''", "answer":0, "answers":["Robbie Coltrane"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played The Title Role In The 1960 Hammer Production The Curse Of The Werewolf", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Reed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played The Title Role In The 1965 British Film The Nanny", "answer":0, "answers":["Bette Davis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Played The Title Role In The Abdomibale Dr Phibes", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincent Price"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the title role in The Abominable Dr Phibes", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincent Price"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who played the younger scrooge in the Classic with Alistair Sim?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Cole"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who plays the character of Chris Kringle aka Santa Claus, in the 1994 film 'Miracle On 34th Street''", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Attenborough"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''", "answer":0, "answers":["Chevy Chase"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who plays the role of the Prime Minister, in the 2003 Christmas film 'Love Actually''", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Grant"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who popularized the Christmas tree in Britain and the U.S.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queen Victoria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Preceded Harold Wilson As Prime Minister?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Alec Douglas Home"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Preceded Mao Tse-Tung?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chiang Kai-Chek"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who presided over the trial of Jesus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pontius Pilate"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who proclaimed thanksgiving a national holiday in 1863", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Provided The Voice Of Charlie In The TV Show 'Charlies Angels''", "answer":0, "answers":["John Forsythe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who ran unsuccesfully against Regan in 1984?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walter Mondale"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who received the nobel peace prize in 1964 for civil rights leadership?", "answer":0, "answers":["Martin Luther King Jr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who released an album called 'Ghost in the Machine'", "answer":0, "answers":["The Police"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled 2112", "answer":0, "answers":["Rush"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled 461 Ocean Boulevard", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Clapton"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Abraxas", "answer":0, "answers":["Santana"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Aja", "answer":0, "answers":["Steely Dan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled All Mod Cons", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jam"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled All Things Must Pass", "answer":0, "answers":["George Harrison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Arrival", "answer":0, "answers":["ABBA"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Autobahn", "answer":0, "answers":["Kraftwerk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Bitches Brew", "answer":0, "answers":["Miles Davis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Blood on the Tracks", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Dylan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Blue", "answer":0, "answers":["Joni Mitchell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Broken English", "answer":0, "answers":["Marianne Faithfull"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Cant Buy a Trill", "answer":0, "answers":["Steely Dan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Catch a Fire", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Marley and the Wailers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Cosmo's Factory", "answer":0, "answers":["Creedence Clearwater Revival"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Deja Vu", "answer":0, "answers":["CSNY"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Destroyer", "answer":0, "answers":["KISS"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Electric Warrior", "answer":0, "answers":["T. Rex"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Exile on Main Street", "answer":0, "answers":["The Rolling Stones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled For Your Pleasure", "answer":0, "answers":["Roxy Music"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Fun House", "answer":0, "answers":["The Stooges"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Gasoline Alley", "answer":0, "answers":["Rod Stewart"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Germ Free Adolescents", "answer":0, "answers":["X-Ray Spex"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Grievous Angel", "answer":0, "answers":["Gram Parsons"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Here Come the Warm Jets", "answer":0, "answers":["Eno"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Horses", "answer":0, "answers":["Patti Smith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Hunky Dory", "answer":0, "answers":["David Bowie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled In Rock", "answer":0, "answers":["Deep Purple"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Innervisions", "answer":0, "answers":["Stevie Wonder"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled John Barleycorn Must Die", "answer":0, "answers":["Traffic"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Kimono my House", "answer":0, "answers":["Sparks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Lark's Tongue in Aspic", "answer":0, "answers":["King Crimson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Layla & other assorted love songs", "answer":0, "answers":["Derek and the Dominos"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Legalize It", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Tosh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Live at Leeds", "answer":0, "answers":["The Who"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Machine Gun Etiquette", "answer":0, "answers":["The Damned"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Machine Head", "answer":0, "answers":["Deep Purple"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Madman Across the Water", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Muswell Hillbillies", "answer":0, "answers":["Kinks"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled My Aim is True", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Costello"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled New Boots and Panties", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Dury"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Next", "answer":0, "answers":["The Sensational Alex Harvey Band"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Out of the Blue", "answer":0, "answers":["ELO"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Oxygene", "answer":0, "answers":["Jean Michel Jarre"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Parallel Lines", "answer":0, "answers":["Blondie"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Physical Graffiti", "answer":0, "answers":["Led Zeppelin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Pretzel Logic", "answer":0, "answers":["Steely Dan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Red Headed Stranger", "answer":0, "answers":["Willie Nelson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Reggatta de Blanc", "answer":0, "answers":["The Police"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Rumours", "answer":0, "answers":["Fleetwood Mac"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Selling England by the Pound", "answer":0, "answers":["Genesis"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Sheet Music", "answer":0, "answers":["10cc"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Slayed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slade"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Stardust", "answer":0, "answers":["Willie Nelson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Sticky Fingers", "answer":0, "answers":["Rolling Stones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Superfly", "answer":0, "answers":["Curtis Mayfield"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Tea for the Tillerman", "answer":0, "answers":["Cat Stevens"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled The Grand Tour", "answer":0, "answers":["George Jones"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled The Pleasure Principle", "answer":0, "answers":["Gary Newman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled The Scream", "answer":0, "answers":["Siouxsie and the Banshees"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled The Stranger", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy Joel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Tonights the Night", "answer":0, "answers":["Neil Young"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Toys in the Attic", "answer":0, "answers":["Aerosmith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Trafalgar", "answer":0, "answers":["Bee Gees"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Trans-Europe Express", "answer":0, "answers":["Kraftwerk"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Transformer", "answer":0, "answers":["Lou Reed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Tusk", "answer":0, "answers":["Fleetwood Mac"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Twelve Dreams of Dr. Sardonicus", "answer":0, "answers":["Spirit"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who released the Pet Shop Boys song `I'm Not Scared' in 1988", "answer":0, "answers":["Eighth Wonder"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who resigned as Russian Premier on Christmas day 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["Mikhail Gorbachev"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who rode naked through the streets of Coventry", "answer":0, "answers":["Lady godiva"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who rode naked through the streets of Coventry?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lady Godiva"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who ruled England at the time of Shakespeare?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth I"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who ruled rome when Christ was born?", "answer":0, "answers":["Augustus Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said 'eureka'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Archimedes"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said 'public service is my motto'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Al Capone"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said \"Veni, vidi, vici\" (I came, I saw, I conquered)?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Julius Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said \"Veni, vidi, vici\" (I came, I saw, I conquered)\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Julius caesar"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Said (Will No-One Rid Me Of This Turbulent Priest)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry II"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said: \"Let them eat cake.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Marie antoinette"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said: \"Let them eat cake\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marie Antoinette"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said: there is nothing in the bible that says i must wear rags", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy graham"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who said: when i look at my children, i say lillian you should have stayed a virgin", "answer":0, "answers":["Lillian carter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sailed to the new world in 'The mayflower'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pilgrims"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang 'I Want My MTV' on the Dire Straits song 'Money For Nothing'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sting"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Sang El Condor Pasa (If I Could)", "answer":0, "answers":["Simon & Garfunkel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang Happy Birthday to John F. Kennedy for his 45th", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn monroe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang Happy Birthday to John F. Kennedy for his 45th?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang Its a Heartache, nothing but a heartache?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bonnie Tyler"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang No More Heroes?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Stranglers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang the song 'Cry' which was the first video on Mtv to use morphing technology through the entire video?", "answer":0, "answers":["Godley and Creme"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang the theme song to the 'Breakfast Club'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Simple Minds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who sang the theme tune to the James Bond. Movie 'The Spy Who Loved Me", "answer":0, "answers":["Carly Simon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who shot Abraham Lincoln?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Wilkes Booth"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who shot J.R. Euing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kristin Sheppard"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack Ruby"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who shot President James Garfield?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Guiteau"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who signed the 'thanksgiving proclamation'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham Lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who starred in Funny Girl and Lawrence of Arabia?", "answer":0, "answers":["Omar Sharif"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who starred in the 1954 Musical remake of 'A star is born' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Judy Garland"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who starred in the 1957 film showboat as June?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ava Gardner"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who started the second Punic war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carthage"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Succceeded Hitler In 1945?", "answer":0, "answers":["Admiral Donitz"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who succeeded Churchill when he resigned in 1955", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir anthony eden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who succeeded Churchill when he resigned in 1955?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Anthony Eden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who succeeded Winston Churchill as Prime Minister of England?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anthony Eden"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who took over from Kennedy after he was assassinated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lyndon B Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who took the title \"Lord Protector of the Commonwelth of England, Scotland, and Ireland\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Cromwell"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who tried to create the 'Great Society'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lyndon B Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Uttered The Immortal lines 'They Think It's All Over, It Is Now''", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenneth Wolstenholme"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wanted to make a coat out of 101 Dalmatians", "answer":0, "answers":["Cruella Devil"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was 'The Elephant Man'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joseph Merrick"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was \"The Mad Monk\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rasputin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was \"The Mad Monk\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Rasputin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was A Tory, then Became A Labour MP And Finally Lead The British Facist Party?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oswald Mosley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was assassinated on December 8, 1980 in New York City?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Lennon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was assassinated on November 22, 1963 in Dallas, Texas?", "answer":0, "answers":["President John F. Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Canada's first Prime Minister", "answer":0, "answers":["John A. Macdonald"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was captain of 'The Mayflower'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Miles Standish"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Captain of the Titanic on her maiden voyage?", "answer":0, "answers":["Edward J. Smith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Cary Grant's female lead in the movie 'To catch a thief?", "answer":0, "answers":["Grace Kelly"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was crowned King of England at Westminster Abbey on Christmas day 1066", "answer":0, "answers":["William The Conqueror"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Declared Dead On New Years Day 1953 At The Age Of 29?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hank Williams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn?", "answer":0, "answers":["George A. Custer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was England's Manager In The 1970 Football World Cup Finals", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Alf Ramsey"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was forced by Indian troops into the Black Hole of Calcutta?", "answer":0, "answers":["British officers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was George Washington's vice_president", "answer":0, "answers":["Adams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was George Washington's vice-president?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Adams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was given the only Nobel Peace Prize award during WWI?", "answer":0, "answers":["International Red Cross"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Henry Bolingbroke's Father", "answer":0, "answers":["John Of Gaunt (The Duke Of Lancaster)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Henry VIII's Last Wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Catherine Parr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Henry VIII's second wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Henry VIII's Third Wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Seymour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Joseph Merrick?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Elephant Man"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was kidnapped on the night of March 1, 1932?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Lindbergh Jr"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was King Arthur's foster-father?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ector"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was King Of England During The Battle Of Agincourt?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry V"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was known as 'the peanut president'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy Carter"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was known as \"the wizard of Menlo Park\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Alva Edison"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Known As Coeur De Lion?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard I (The Lionheart)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was made Lord Mayor of London in 1397, 1398, 1406 and 1419?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard (Dick) Whittington"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Margaret Thatcher?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prime Minister of Great Britan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis XVI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was nick named Hanoi Jane in 1972 because of her enemy propaganda broadcasts from Vietnam?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Fonda"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Nick-Named (The Desert Fox)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Field Marshal Rommel"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Ousted By Corazon Aquino In 1986", "answer":0, "answers":["Ferdinand Marcos"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was patricia hurst with the night she was kidnapped", "answer":0, "answers":["Steven weed"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was President Of America At The Outbreak Of World War II?", "answer":0, "answers":["Franklin D Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was President of the USA from 1953 till 1961?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dwight D. Eisenhower"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was President Of The USA In 1952 A) Harry Truman, B) Dwight Eisenhower, C= Lyndon Johnson", "answer":0, "answers":["A= Harry Truman"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Prime Minister When Edward VIII Abdicated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Baldwin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Ptolemy Dionysius Related To As Both Brother And Husband", "answer":0, "answers":["Cleopatra"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Quoted As Saying 'Ask Not What Your Country Can Do For You But What You Can Do For Your Country''", "answer":0, "answers":["John F Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was responsible for the infamous assination attempt on then President Reagan?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Hinkley Jr."], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Scrooge's dead business partner in 'A Christmas Carol'", "answer":0, "answers":["Jacob Marley"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Shot Dead In Dallas On 24th November 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Lee Harvey Oswald"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was Shot In Dallas On 24 th November 1963", "answer":0, "answers":["Lee Harvey Oswald"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The 1st wife of henry Viii", "answer":0, "answers":["Catherine Of Aragon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The 2nd Wife Of Henry Viii", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The 3rd Wife Of Henry Viii", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Seymour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The 4th Wife Of Henry Viii", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Of Cleeves"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the British Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Second World War?", "answer":0, "answers":["Neville Chamberlain"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969", "answer":0, "answers":["Harold Wilson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the composer of 'The Nutcracker' ballet? (Handel, Bach, Tchaikovsky, Schubert)", "answer":0, "answers":["Tchaikovsky"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the cult leader of the Waco Siege in 1993?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Koresh"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the eighties group that was named after the inventor of the radio?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tesla"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the father of Elizabeth I?", "answer":0, "answers":["Henry VIII"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the female Prime Minister of England throughout the eighties?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marget Thatcher"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the female star of 'Bewitched'", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth Montgomery"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the female star of in the tv version of 'Bewitched'", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth Montgomery"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first (and last) catholic president?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Fitzerald Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first African-American female to win a Wimbledon Tennis event? In both 1957 And 1958", "answer":0, "answers":["Althea Gibson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first British monarch to broadcast a Christmas message to the nation?", "answer":0, "answers":["George the Fifth (in 1932)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First Catholic President Of The United States", "answer":0, "answers":["Catholic F"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first chancellor of West Germany after WW II", "answer":0, "answers":["Adenauer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first chancellor of West Germany after WW II?", "answer":0, "answers":["Konrad Adenauer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First Christian Emperor Of Rome", "answer":0, "answers":["Constantine The Great"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first dog in space ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Laika"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first English monarch to have a Christmas tree? (Elizabeth I, King George II, King James VI, Queen Victoria", "answer":0, "answers":["Queen Victoria"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first female American astronaut ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sally Ride"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first fully Danish king of England ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Canute the Great"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first ghost appear to scrooge in the dickens classic a Christmas carol?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marleys Ghost"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first incumbent u.s. president to survive being shot", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronald reagan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first man to reach the North Pole ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Edwin Peary"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first person to break the sound barrier?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chuck Yeager"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first person to swim the English Channel?", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Matthew Webb"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First President Of The United States?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Washington"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First Roman Emperor", "answer":0, "answers":["Augustus (Gaius Julius Octavianus)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First To Sing On The 1984 Band Aid Single", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Young"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first u.s president born outside the orginal 13 states", "answer":0, "answers":["Abraham lincoln"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First Us President To Take Up Residence In The Whitehouse", "answer":0, "answers":["John Adams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first Windsor monarch of the UK?", "answer":0, "answers":["George V (reigned 1910-1936)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first woman elected to lead a european democracy", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret thatcher"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first woman in space?", "answer":0, "answers":["Valentina Tereshkova"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the first woman to be shot by the FBI?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bonnie Parker (of Bonnie and Clyde fame)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The First X Factor Winner To Have A Christmas Number One", "answer":0, "answers":["Shayne Ward"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the founder of Live Aid?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Geldof"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the instigator of the breakaway World Series Cricket in 1977?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kerry Packer"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the last American president to sport facial hair?", "answer":0, "answers":["Taft"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Last British Monarch Born Abroad?", "answer":0, "answers":["King George II"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Last British Monarch To Lead His Forces Into Battle?", "answer":0, "answers":["George II"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the last British Viceroy of India?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Louis Mountbatten"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Last King To Sit On The English Throne", "answer":0, "answers":["George VI"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the last of the apache warrior chiefs", "answer":0, "answers":["Geronimo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the last to sit on the peacock throne", "answer":0, "answers":["Shah mohammed reza pahlavi"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the lead singer for Creedence Clearwater Revival, and recently released 'Blue Moon Swamp'?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Fogerty"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the lead singer of the Cure?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Smith"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the leader of the Khmer Rouge?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pol Pot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the man convicted of masterminding the 1969 LaBianca-Tate murders, later to become known as the Helter Skelter killings?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Manson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the most famous leader of the Carthagenians?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hannibal"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the mother of Elizabeth I?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Boleyn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Mother Of James 1st Of England?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Queen Of Scots"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the mother of James I of England (VI of Scotland )?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mary Queen Of Scots"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the New Zealand mountaineer who in 1953, together with Sherpa Tenzing Norgay, became the first person to reach the summit of Mount Everest", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Edmund Hillary"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Only British Pope?", "answer":0, "answers":["Adrian IV"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the only survivor of Custer's last stand?", "answer":0, "answers":["His horse"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the President of Egypt in 1956 who nationalized the Suez Canal causing British and French troops to invade the region", "answer":0, "answers":["Gamal Abdul Nasser"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was the Queen Of The Iceni Tribe Of England Who Led An Uprising Against The Romans?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boudica"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the ruler of the Principality of Monaco who married actress Grace Kelly in 1956", "answer":0, "answers":["Prince Ranier"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the ruler of the USSR from 1917-22?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vladimir Lenin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the second man to set foot on the moon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Edwin \"Buzz\" Aldrin\""], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the second President of the USA?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Adams"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the second to set foot on the moon", "answer":0, "answers":["Buz aldrin"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was the Taj Mahal built in memory of?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mumtaj Mahal"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Very First Presenter Of The UK National Lottery Draw", "answer":0, "answers":["Noel Edmonds"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Was The Youngest British Prime Minister?", "answer":0, "answers":["William Pitt (The Younger)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was UK Labour cabinet minister and social reformer Frank Pakenham better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Longford (7th Earl of Longford)"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was Ulysses' son, who grew to manhood in his absence?", "answer":0, "answers":["Telemachus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was, \"First in war, first in peace and first in the hearts of his countrymen\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Washington"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who was, \"First in war, first in peace and first in the hearts of his countrymen\"", "answer":0, "answers":["George washington"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Were 'Kissing In The Back Row'' Of A Movie In 1974", "answer":0, "answers":["The Drifters"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who were Balthazar, Melchior and Caspar", "answer":0, "answers":["The 3 Wise Men"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who were Balthazar, Melchior and Caspar?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Three Wise Men"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who were the first people to be elected into the Aviation Hall Of Fame?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wright Brothers"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who won the 1968 oregon democratic primary", "answer":0, "answers":["Eugene mccarthy"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote 'Auld Lang Syne'", "answer":0, "answers":["Robery Burn / Henry Viii"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote 'The Starry Messenger'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Galileo"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote A Famous Diary Between 1660 & 1669?", "answer":0, "answers":["Samuel Pepys"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote Auld Lange Syne?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Burns"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote How the Grinch Stole Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Seuss"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote The 1951 Novel The Catcher in the Rye?", "answer":0, "answers":["J.D Salinger"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote the book 'The Shining' on which the 1980 Stanley Kubrick film was based", "answer":0, "answers":["Stephen King"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote The Book Alice In Wonderland", "answer":0, "answers":["Lewis Carrol"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote the book, that was the basis for the 1982 animated film, 'The Snowman''", "answer":0, "answers":["Raymond Briggs"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote the children's book 'How The Grinch Stole Christmas''", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Seuss"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wrote the Novel 'The Witching Hour'", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Rice"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who wrote The Strange Case of Dr Jeckyll and Mr Hyde", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Louis Stevenson"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who Wtote The Book 'How The Grinch Stole Christmas'", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr Seuss"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Who, in 1909, became the first man to fly across the English Channel", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis Bleriot"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose army did Admiral Nelson defeat at the battle of Trafalgar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Napoleon"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose Death In 1965 Prompted President Johnson That All American Flags The World Over Be Flown At Half Mast A Mark Of Respect Never Before Accorded To A Foreigner", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose Election slogan Was (You've Never Had It So Good)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harold Macmillian, 1959"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose epitaph reads, free at last, free at last, thank god almighty, i'm free at last", "answer":0, "answers":["Martin luther king jr."], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose radio production of War Of The World's caused panic in America in 1938?", "answer":0, "answers":["Orson Welles"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Whose Scary Movie Character Has The real name is Charles Lee Ray", "answer":0, "answers":["Chucky"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Why did Richard John Bingham make the news in the 1970s?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Lucan"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Why do we decorate with holly at Christmas?", "answer":0, "answers":["Represents the crown of thorns worn by jesus"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Why is the day after Christmas named Boxing Day?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Rich Gave Presents To The Poor"], "source":""},
  {"question":"William the First was crowned on Christmas day, but in what year", "answer":0, "answers":["1066"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With three words complete this movie trailer catch line for the film Alien. 'In space no one can_____'", "answer":0, "answers":["Hear you scream"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With two words, complete this BBC radio signal to the French Resistance in the film The Longest Day. The long sobs of autumns violins wound my heart with _____", "answer":0, "answers":["Monotonous langour"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With Which Band Did The Jimi Hendrix Experience 's Record Producer/Manager Chas Chadler Make His Name", "answer":0, "answers":["The Animals"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Of Leatherface", "answer":0, "answers":["Texas Chainsaw Massacre"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With Which Ship Did Francis Drake Circumnavigate The World?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pelican, Renamed The Golden Hind After Clearing Cape Horn"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With Which War Is Florence Nightingale Associated", "answer":0, "answers":["Crimean"], "source":""},
  {"question":"With With Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface", "answer":0, "answers":["Texas Chansaw Massacre"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Xavier Roberts was the name associated with which eighties toy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cabbage Patch Kids"], "source":""},
  {"question":"Yorkshireman William Strickland is believed to have brought the first what to Britain from North America in 1526?", "answer":0, "answers":["Turkey"], "source":""}
]